was O
in O
early O
stages O
of O
developing O
a O
relaunch O
of O
the O
franchise O
with O
Zak B-PER
Penn I-PER
in O
talks O
to O
write O
a O
treatment O
and O
interest O
in O
getting O
Michael B-PER
B. I-PER
Jordan I-PER
attached O
to O
star O
. O

The O
Morrison B-LOC
Formation I-LOC
records O
a O
time O
when O
the O
local O
environment O
was O
dominated O
by O
gigantic O
sauropod O
dinosaurs O
. O

He O
also O
won O
three O
EuroBasket B-MISC
titles O
in O
2009 O
, O
2011 O
, O
and O
2015 O
, O
a O
silver O
medal O
in O
2007 O
, O
and O
a O
bronze O
medal O
in O
2013 O
. O

The O
libretto O
of O
" O
Doctor B-MISC
Atomic I-MISC
" O
, O
written O
by O
Peter B-PER
Sellars I-PER
, O
draws O
on O
original O
source O
material O
, O
including O
personal O
memoirs O
, O
recorded O
interviews O
, O
technical O
manuals O
of O
nuclear O
physics O
, O
declassified O
government O
documents O
, O
and O
the O
poetry O
of O
the O
" O
Bhagavad B-MISC
Gita I-MISC
" O
, O
John B-PER
Donne I-PER
, O
Charles B-PER
Baudelaire I-PER
, O
and O
Muriel B-PER
Rukeyser I-PER
. O

For O
, O
until O
some O
people O
came O
from O
James B-PER
, O
he O
used O
to O
eat O
with O
the O
Gentiles B-PER
; O
but O
when O
they O
came O
, O
he O
began O
to O
draw O
back O
and O
separated O
himself O
, O
because O
he O
was O
afraid O
of O
the O
circumcised O
. O

Chrysler B-ORG
struggled O
to O
adapt O
to O
the O
changing O
environment O
of O
the O
1970 O
s O
. O

In O
the O
game O
, O
the O
Lions B-ORG
got O
off O
to O
a O
hot O
start O
, O
going O
up O
14 O
– O
0 O
in O
the O
first O
quarter O
. O

It O
is O
named O
after O
Heinrich B-PER
Jung I-PER
, O
who O
first O
studied O
this O
inequality O
in O
1901 O
. O

Her O
style O
has O
been O
described O
as O
" O
glamorous O
" O
meets O
" O
sexy O
elegance O
" O
by O
Holt B-ORG
Renfrew I-ORG
executives O
. O

Conservative O
authorities O
, O
as O
part O
of O
their O
promulgation O
of O
a O
dynamic O
" O
Halakha B-MISC
" O
, O
often O
cite O
the O
manner O
in O
which O
the O
sages O
of O
old O
used O
rabbinic O
statues O
( O
" O
Takkanah O
" O
) O
that O
enabled O
to O
bypass O
prohibitions O
in O
the O
Pentateuch I-MISC
, O
like O
the O
" O
Prozbul I-MISC
" O
or O
" O
Heter I-MISC
I'ska I-MISC
" O
. O

His O
first O
league O
win O
as O
manager O
came O
on O
11 O
September O
2010 O
, O
a O
2 O
– O
1 O
win O
against O
Udinese B-ORG
at O
the O
San B-LOC
Siro I-LOC
. O

He O
decided O
to O
move O
to O
Limassol B-LOC
where O
he O
established O
his O
new O
headquarters O
. O

Hyderabad B-LOC
will O
remain O
as O
a O
joint O
capital O
for O
not O
exceeding O
ten O
years O
. O

She O
is O
the O
favorite O
musician O
of O
Neil B-PER
deGrasse I-PER
Tyson I-PER
. O

In O
summer O
1971 O
, O
film O
producer O
Arthur B-PER
P. I-PER
Jacobs I-PER
optioned O
the O
film O
rights O
to O
" O
Dune B-MISC
" O
, O
but O
died O
in O
summer O
1973 O
, O
while O
plans O
for O
the O
film O
( O
including O
David B-PER
Lean I-PER
already O
attached O
to O
direct O
) O
were O
still O
in O
development O
. O

His O
father O
, O
Mao B-PER
Yichang I-PER
, O
was O
a O
formerly O
impoverished O
peasant O
who O
had O
become O
one O
of O
the O
wealthiest O
farmers O
in O
Shaoshan B-LOC
. O

Slowing O
the O
set O
time O
of O
plaster O
of O
Paris B-LOC
products O
( O
most O
widely O
used O
in O
gypsum O
plaster O
wall O
work O
and O
artwork O
casting O
) O
is O
typically O
achieved O
by O
the O
simple O
introduction O
of O
almost O
any O
acid O
diluted O
into O
the O
mixing O
water O
. O

The O
Mystery B-ORG
Writers I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
have O
named O
their O
awards O
for O
excellence O
in O
the O
genre O
the O
" O
Edgars B-MISC
" O
. O

On O
27 O
January O
, O
he O
scored O
the O
only O
goal O
in O
a O
1 O
– O
0 O
away O
win O
against O
Panthrakikos B-ORG
. O

Among O
passerines O
, O
which O
are O
usually O
quite O
secondary O
besides O
corvids O
, O
they O
've O
been O
known O
to O
hunt O
various O
larks O
( O
up O
to O
nearly O
11 O
% O
of O
the O
diet O
in O
Georgia B-LOC
) O
, O
shrikes O
, O
swallows O
, O
accentors O
, O
Old I-MISC
World I-MISC
flycatchers O
( O
at O
least O
10 O
different O
species O
) O
, O
thrushes O
, O
pipits O
, O
starlings O
, O
buntings O
, O
finches O
and O
Old I-MISC
world I-MISC
sparrows O
. O

According O
to O
GRECO B-ORG
in O
2007 O
, O
corruption O
should O
be O
taken O
into O
account O
in O
the O
Finnish B-MISC
system O
of O
election O
funds O
better O
. O

At O
Wimbledon B-LOC
, O
she O
was O
the O
runner-up O
in O
2001 O
and O
2006 O
. O

It O
features O
songs O
recorded O
in O
the O
RCA B-ORG
studios O
with O
a O
full O
orchestra O
and O
backing O
vocals O
. O

J. B-PER
M. I-PER
W. I-PER
Turner I-PER
painted O
several O
watercolours O
of O
the O
castle O
. O

A O
common O
use O
was O
for O
emoticons O
, O
with O
WOBTAX B-ORG
and O
VICTORY I-MISC
both O
producing O
convincing O
smiley O
faces O
. O

However O
, O
the O
lifting O
of O
strict O
genre O
licensing O
restrictions O
saw O
the O
network O
remove O
the O
last O
of O
its O
music O
programming O
at O
the O
end O
of O
August O
2017 O
for O
a O
schedule O
of O
generic O
off-network O
family O
sitcoms O
, O
Cancom-compliant B-ORG
lifestyle O
programming O
, O
and O
reality O
programming O
. O

The O
prefect O
had O
Ammonius B-PER
tortured O
to O
death O
, O
whereupon O
the O
Patriarch O
honored O
him O
as O
a O
martyr O
. O

In O
applications O
, O
when O
distances O
do O
n't O
match O
exactly O
, O
Procrustes B-PER
analysis O
aims O
to O
relate O
two O
point O
sets O
as O
close O
as O
possible O
via O
rigid O
transformations O
, O
usually O
using O
singular O
value O
decomposition O
. O

Kenneth B-PER
Burke I-PER
asserted O
humans O
use O
rhetoric O
to O
resolve O
conflicts O
by O
identifying O
shared O
characteristics O
and O
interests O
in O
symbols O
. O

Over O
100 O
have O
been O
identified O
in O
Scotland B-LOC
alone O
. O

The O
most O
recent O
significant O
migrations O
came O
as O
a O
result O
of O
the O
1991 O
– O
1995 O
Croatian B-MISC
War I-MISC
of I-MISC
Independence I-MISC
. O

He O
spends O
the O
winter O
there O
with O
his O
wife O
, O
played O
by O
Shelley B-PER
Duvall I-PER
, O
and O
their O
young O
son O
, O
who O
displays O
paranormal O
abilities O
. O

Costa B-LOC
Rica I-LOC
's O
economy O
was O
historically O
based O
on O
agriculture O
, O
and O
this O
has O
had O
a O
large O
cultural O
impact O
through O
the O
years O
. O

They O
faced O
Portugal B-LOC
in O
the O
semi-finals O
. O

The O
antiprotons O
used O
in O
these O
experiments O
were O
cooled O
by O
decelerating O
them O
with O
the O
Antiproton I-MISC
Decelerator I-MISC
, O
passing O
them O
through O
a O
thin O
sheet O
of O
foil O
, O
and O
finally O
capturing O
them O
in O
a O
Penning–Malmberg B-LOC
trap O
. O

In O
1967 O
the O
Conservatives B-MISC
unexpectedly O
won O
control O
of O
the O
Inner B-ORG
London I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
and O
the O
party O
leadership O
was O
horrified O
to O
discover O
that O
their O
newly O
elected O
councillors O
were O
going O
to O
try O
to O
break O
up O
comprehensive O
schools O
and O
replace O
them O
with O
secondary O
modern O
and O
grammar O
schools O
. O

The O
intonation O
resembles O
the O
Scanian B-MISC
dialect O
spoken O
in O
nearby O
Scania B-LOC
, O
the O
southernmost O
province O
of O
Sweden B-LOC
. O

All O
of O
the O
" O
MAX B-MISC
" O
songs O
on O
" O
MAX2 B-MISC
" O
received O
foot-ratings O
, O
excluding O
songs O
that O
were O
removed O
. O

The O
third O
and O
last O
KERNAL B-MISC
" O
ROM O
revision O
was O
introduced O
on O
the O
250466 O
motherboard O
( O
late O
breadbin O
models O
with O
41464 O
RAM O
) O
and O
is O
found O
in O
all O
C64Cs B-MISC
. O

The O
rockfowl O
are O
distributed O
in O
west O
and O
western O
Central B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
in O
Guinea B-LOC
, O
Sierra B-LOC
Leone I-LOC
, O
Liberia B-LOC
, O
Ivory B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
, O
Ghana B-LOC
( O
white-necked O
rockfowl O
) O
, O
Nigeria B-LOC
, O
Cameroon B-LOC
, O
Equatorial B-LOC
Guinea I-LOC
, O
Gabon B-LOC
, O
the O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
the I-LOC
Congo I-LOC
, O
and O
the O
Central B-LOC
African I-LOC
Republic I-LOC
( O
grey-necked O
rockfowl O
) O
. O

He O
has O
been O
a O
member O
of O
the O
classical O
crossover O
group O
" O
Il B-ORG
Divo I-ORG
" O
since O
2004 O
, O
who O
has O
sold O
over O
28 O
million O
copies O
worldwide O
discs O
. O

The O
tour O
included O
a O
set O
at O
Woodstock B-MISC
' I-MISC
94 I-MISC
broadcast O
on O
pay-per-view O
and O
seen O
in O
as O
many O
as O
24 O
" O
million O
homes O
. O

Rodents O
, O
rabbits O
, O
and O
hares O
often O
serve O
as O
reservoir O
hosts O
, O
but O
waterborne O
infection O
accounts O
for O
5 O
to O
10 O
% O
of O
all O
tularemia O
in O
the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
. O

There O
, O
in O
turn O
, O
the O
winds O
curve O
southward O
towards O
the O
Iberian B-LOC
Peninsula I-LOC
. O

The O
excavations O
in O
the O
nympheum O
only O
reveal O
the O
foundations O
and O
it O
is O
difficult O
to O
interpret O
the O
ornaments O
of O
the O
facade O
from O
only O
a O
few O
fine O
marble O
remains O
, O
but O
no O
doubt O
these O
were O
similar O
to O
those O
in O
other O
Roman B-MISC
cities O
. O

Due O
to O
this O
, O
he O
was O
ineligible O
to O
join O
the O
MLBPA B-ORG
. O

The O
gathering O
was O
the O
biggest O
international O
diplomatic O
gathering O
ever O
held O
in O
Northern B-LOC
Ireland I-LOC
. O

He O
had O
a O
six-episode O
stint O
as O
host O
of O
the O
game O
show O
" O
Make B-MISC
the I-MISC
Connection I-MISC
" O
on O
NBC B-ORG
in O
1955 O
. O

A O
proponent O
of O
civil O
rights O
, O
women O
's O
emancipation O
, O
and O
anti-imperialistic O
ideas O
, O
she O
was O
an O
important O
figure O
in O
India B-LOC
's O
struggle O
for O
independence O
from O
colonial O
rule O
. O

where O
" O
γ O
" O
is O
the O
Euler–Mascheroni B-PER
constant O
and O
ζ O
' O
is O
the O
derivative O
of O
the O
Riemann B-PER
zeta O
function O
. O

In O
1974 O
, O
Dio B-ORG
sang O
on O
the O
Roger B-PER
Glover I-PER
conducted O
and O
produced O
concept O
album O
" O
The B-MISC
Butterfly I-MISC
Ball I-MISC
and I-MISC
the I-MISC
Grasshopper I-MISC
's I-MISC
Feast I-MISC
" O
. O

The O
show O
gives O
the O
hosts O
a O
convenient O
soapbox O
to O
feature O
their O
opinions O
on O
such O
issues O
as O
film O
colorization O
, O
letterboxing O
, O
the O
MPAA B-ORG
film O
rating O
system O
, O
product O
placement O
, O
independent O
filmmaking O
, O
and O
social O
issues O
. O

Moreover O
, O
various O
properties O
of O
a O
crystal O
, O
including O
electrical O
conductivity O
, O
electrical O
permittivity O
, O
and O
Young B-PER
's O
modulus O
, O
may O
be O
different O
in O
different O
directions O
in O
a O
crystal O
. O

The O
opening O
began O
with O
images O
of O
the O
Golden B-LOC
Gate I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
and O
flashing O
shots O
of O
the O
triquetra O
symbol O
in O
a O
circle O
. O

In O
1909 O
the O
nine O
locomotives O
numbered O
above O
100 O
were O
transferred O
to O
the O
London B-ORG
and I-ORG
North I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
and O
renumbered O
in O
the O
2600 O
s O
. O

Further O
east O
, O
the O
salinity O
increases O
and O
the O
freshwater O
fish O
species O
are O
completely O
replaced O
by O
euryhaline O
marine O
ones O
, O
until O
the O
river O
reaches O
Gravesend B-LOC
, O
at O
which O
point O
conditions O
become O
fully O
marine O
and O
the O
fish O
fauna O
resembles O
that O
of O
the O
adjacent O
North B-LOC
Sea I-LOC
and O
includes O
both O
euryhaline O
and O
stenohaline O
marine O
species O
. O

He O
was O
signed O
by O
the O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Giants I-ORG
as O
an O
undrafted O
free O
agent O
in O
2005 O
. O

Rinderpest O
continued O
to O
infect O
90 O
% O
of O
Africa B-LOC
's O
cattle O
. O

The O
territory O
of O
Belgium B-LOC
is O
almost O
equally O
divided O
between O
the O
two O
nations O
of O
Flemish B-LOC
Flanders B-LOC
and O
Francophone B-LOC
Wallonia B-LOC
. O

Between O
1993 O
and O
1996 O
, O
the O
Fleetwood B-MISC
Suburban B-MISC
was O
used O
instead O
of O
the O
DeVille B-MISC
for O
most O
funeral O
coaches O
and O
limousines O
produced O
during O
these O
years O
. O

There O
is O
a O
obelisk O
monument O
at O
Arlington B-LOC
National I-LOC
Cemetery I-LOC
where O
he O
is O
buried O
. O

He O
was O
the O
indisputable O
leader O
of O
" O
antique O
" O
( O
pre-classical O
) O
archaeology O
in O
Bulgaria B-LOC
. O

It O
had O
become O
clear O
that O
the O
Soviet B-LOC
Union I-LOC
was O
beginning O
to O
loosen O
up O
. O

In O
1992 O
, O
Azerbaijan B-LOC
became O
member O
of O
the O
Economic B-ORG
Cooperation I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
. O

England B-LOC
equalised O
through O
a O
Geoff B-PER
Hurst I-PER
header O
within O
six O
minutes O
and O
went O
ahead O
late O
in O
the O
second O
half O
through O
Martin B-PER
Peters I-PER
. O

To O
explain O
the O
name O
: O
if O
a O
localizing O
subcategory O
" O
S O
" O
of O
a O
compactly O
generated O
triangulated O
category O
" O
D O
" O
is O
generated O
by O
a O
set O
of O
objects O
, O
then O
there O
is O
a O
Bousfield B-PER
localization O
functor O
with O
kernel O
" O
S O
" O
. O

The O
suborder O
Salamandroidea B-MISC
contains O
the O
advanced O
salamanders O
. O

In O
1984 O
, O
Turkey B-LOC
unilaterally O
declared O
that O
it O
would O
ensure O
a O
flow O
of O
at O
least O
per O
second O
, O
or O
per O
year O
, O
into O
Syria B-LOC
, O
and O
in O
1987 O
a O
bilateral O
treaty O
to O
that O
effect O
was O
signed O
between O
the O
two O
countries O
. O

The O
chicane O
was O
removed O
in O
1985 O
after O
the O
track O
lost O
its O
Formula B-MISC
One I-MISC
race O
in O
1981 O
. O

On O
5 O
October O
, O
he O
debuted O
for O
the O
club O
in O
a O
4 O
– O
0 O
win O
against O
Arouca B-LOC
, O
scoring O
his O
side O
's O
fourth O
goal O
. O

He O
became O
interim O
pilot O
upon O
Marcel B-PER
Lachemann I-PER
's O
resignation O
on O
August O
6 O
, O
and O
had O
directed O
them O
to O
a O
5 O
– O
9 O
record O
when O
he O
was O
hospitalized O
for O
a O
blood O
clot O
in O
his O
leg O
on O
August O
20 O
. O

Clemson B-ORG
won O
the O
2019 O
national O
championship O
. O

In O
March O
2013 O
he O
was O
reportedly O
targeted O
by O
armed O
men O
in O
Puerto B-LOC
Caimito I-LOC
but O
came O
out O
unharmed O
. O

Using O
Flynn B-PER
's O
taxonomy O
, O
these O
two O
schemes O
of O
dealing O
with O
data O
are O
generally O
referred O
to O
as O
single O
instruction O
stream O
, O
multiple O
data O
stream O
( O
SIMD O
) O
and O
single O
instruction O
stream O
, O
single O
data O
stream O
( O
SISD O
) O
, O
respectively O
. O

Expansion O
of O
the O
Ottoman B-LOC
Empire I-LOC
disrupted O
the O
steady O
development O
and O
Turks B-MISC
occupied O
lands O
here O
in O
1543 O
. O

The O
Library B-LOC
of I-LOC
Congress I-LOC
listed O
more O
than O
50 O
books O
written O
about O
her O
in O
1998 O
, O
and O
that O
number O
has O
continued O
to O
grow O
, O
as O
have O
the O
number O
of O
scholarly O
articles O
, O
estimated O
as O
1000 O
at O
that O
time O
. O

The O
collection O
includes O
dance O
music O
, O
secular O
music O
, O
music O
for O
Ramadan B-MISC
and O
other O
festivals O
, O
and O
music O
for O
animistic O
rituals O
. O

In O
a O
study O
published O
in O
the O
" O
European B-MISC
Journal I-MISC
of I-MISC
Clinical I-MISC
Nutrition I-MISC
" O
, O
the O
frequency O
of O
consumption O
of O
57 O
foods O
/ O
drinks O
of O
4000 O
children O
at O
the O
age O
of O
four O
and O
a O
half O
were O
collected O
by O
maternal O
report O
. O

They O
are O
volcanic O
in O
origin O
, O
the O
peaks O
of O
volcanoes O
which O
were O
active O
in O
Pleistocene B-LOC
times O
. O

He O
was O
also O
a O
reserve O
for O
the O
Natal B-LOC
rugby O
team O
, O
without O
ever O
actually O
playing O
for O
the O
province O
. O

He O
received O
his O
primary O
and O
secondary O
education O
in O
Maryland B-LOC
. O

When O
he O
was O
rebuffed O
there O
he O
traveled O
to O
Belgium B-LOC
, O
where O
in O
1889 O
a O
financier O
offered O
to O
provide O
him O
with O
arms O
and O
money O
in O
exchange O
for O
the O
kingdom O
's O
mineral O
rights O
. O

In O
medieval O
times O
, O
when O
the O
names O
of O
Lynkestis B-LOC
and O
Orestis B-PER
had O
become O
obsolete O
, O
Pelagonia B-LOC
acquired O
a O
broader O
meaning O
. O

Their O
route O
led O
them O
through O
Persia B-LOC
, O
along O
the O
southern O
and O
eastern O
shores O
of O
the O
Caspian B-LOC
Sea I-LOC
, O
and O
certainly O
through O
Talas B-LOC
, O
north-east O
of O
Tashkent B-LOC
. O

And O
at O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
, O
recovered O
Havelberg B-LOC
, O
which O
had O
been O
lost O
since O
983 O
. O

During O
1985 O
- O
87 O
, O
the O
line O
to O
Norwich B-LOC
was O
electrified O
and O
through O
electric O
working O
commenced O
in O
May O
1987 O
. O

From O
2016 O
to O
2019 O
, O
a O
new O
version O
of O
the O
ECMAScript B-MISC
standard O
was O
published O
each O
year O
, O
but O
the O
scope O
of O
changes O
was O
much O
smaller O
than O
the O
5th O
or O
6th O
editions O
. O

They O
are O
named O
after O
two O
nearby O
municipalities O
: O
Adršpach B-LOC
, O
and O
Teplice B-LOC
nad I-LOC
Metují I-LOC
. O

After O
World B-MISC
War I-MISC
II I-MISC
, O
during O
Esperanto B-MISC
events O
a O
common O
currency O
was O
used O
, O
but O
the O
management O
has O
stopped O
at O
the O
end O
of O
the O
20th O
century O
. O

There O
is O
a O
complex O
relationship O
between O
Azerbaijan B-LOC
's O
balance O
of O
trade O
, O
inflation O
, O
measured O
by O
the O
consumer O
price O
index O
and O
the O
value O
of O
its O
currency O
. O

The O
dispute O
was O
initiated O
by O
the O
depression O
in O
trade O
which O
followed O
the O
Crimean B-MISC
War I-MISC
and O
saw O
the O
local O
coal O
owners O
successfully O
impose O
a O
reduction O
in O
wages O
. O

The O
undulating O
courses O
of O
two O
rivers O
, O
the O
Hondo B-LOC
and O
the O
Sarstoon B-LOC
River I-LOC
, O
define O
much O
of O
the O
course O
of O
the O
country O
's O
northern O
and O
southern O
boundaries O
. O

On O
February O
7 O
, O
1985 O
, O
he O
was O
released O
after O
the O
signing O
of O
Brian B-PER
Sipe I-PER
. O

When O
Christianity B-MISC
was O
on O
the O
advance O
, O
pagan O
myths O
were O
Christianized O
; O
when O
it O
was O
in O
retreat O
, O
Bible I-MISC
stories O
and O
Christian I-MISC
saints O
lost O
their O
mythological O
importance O
to O
the O
culture O
. O

Harry B-PER
Innes I-PER
presided O
over O
the O
trial O
, O
which O
commenced O
November O
11 O
. O

He O
started O
for O
Bath B-ORG
in O
the O
victorious O
1998 B-MISC
Heineken I-MISC
Cup I-MISC
Final I-MISC
as O
they O
defeated O
Brive B-ORG
. O

In O
the O
Ogasawara B-LOC
islands O
, O
they O
prey O
on O
the O
indigenous O
snails O
and O
seedlings O
. O

In O
her O
1980 O
autobiography O
, O
Shelley B-PER
Winters I-PER
claimed O
to O
have O
had O
a O
2-year O
affair O
with O
him O
, O
during O
which O
time O
he O
was O
considering O
separation O
from O
his O
wife O
. O

In O
1872 O
he O
was O
elected O
chief O
rabbi O
of O
Pécs B-LOC
, O
Hungary B-LOC
, O
remaining O
there O
eight O
years O
. O

At O
Alderley B-LOC
Edge I-LOC
in O
Cheshire B-LOC
, O
carbon O
dates O
have O
established O
mining O
at O
around O
2280 O
to O
1890 O
BC O
( O
at O
95 O
% O
probability O
) O
. O

He O
was O
dismissed O
by O
critics O
when O
he O
claimed O
that O
he O
could O
beat O
the O
Australian B-MISC
team O
; O
prior O
to O
the O
game O
, O
the O
Australians B-MISC
were O
undefeated O
on O
the O
tour O
and O
had O
won O
22 O
of O
their O
36 O
games O
. O

With O
the O
advent O
of O
surrealism O
as O
a O
poetic O
movement O
, O
anagrams O
regained O
the O
artistic O
respect O
they O
had O
had O
in O
the O
Baroque B-PER
period O
. O

Traditionally O
, O
the O
dabakan O
is O
considered O
a O
masculine O
instrument O
by O
the O
Maranao B-LOC
and O
a O
feminine O
instrument O
by O
the O
Maguindanao B-LOC
but O
as O
a O
sign O
of O
the O
times O
, O
one O
could O
see O
both O
men O
and O
women O
handling O
the O
dabakan O
. O

The O
Cham B-MISC
are O
descendants O
of O
refugees O
from O
the O
various O
wars O
of O
the O
historical O
kingdom O
of O
Champa B-LOC
. O

They O
built O
their O
synagogue O
on O
the O
banks O
of O
the O
Gera B-LOC
river O
and O
used O
it O
from O
1840 O
until O
1884 O
. O

A O
sequel O
to O
" O
First B-MISC
Blood I-MISC
" O
( O
1982 O
) O
, O
it O
is O
the O
second O
installment O
in O
the O
" O
Rambo I-MISC
" O
franchise O
, O
followed O
by O
" O
Rambo B-MISC
III I-MISC
" O
. O

Since O
then O
, O
the O
impact O
of O
the O
border O
war O
with O
Ethiopia B-LOC
, O
and O
continued O
army O
mobilisation O
, O
has O
contributed O
to O
the O
lack O
of O
a O
skilled O
workforce O
. O

Jeremy B-PER
Bentham I-PER
and O
John B-PER
Stuart I-PER
Mill I-PER
are O
influential O
proponents O
of O
this O
school O
of O
thought O
. O

When O
he O
was O
eleven O
, O
he O
became O
the O
youngest O
trumpeter O
with O
the O
National B-ORG
Youth I-ORG
Jazz I-ORG
Orchestra I-ORG
. O

During O
World B-MISC
War I-MISC
II I-MISC
, O
the O
catacombs O
served O
as O
a O
hiding O
place O
for O
partisans O
and O
natural O
shelter O
for O
civilians O
, O
who O
were O
escaping O
air O
plane O
bombing O
. O

The O
FDA B-ORG
revised O
its O
prescribing O
information O
on O
metformin O
in O
2016 O
. O

It O
became O
a O
model O
for O
conservation O
programs O
that O
were O
implemented O
in O
the O
period O
after O
World B-MISC
War I-MISC
II I-MISC
. O

Screenwriter O
Jeffrey B-PER
Boam I-PER
is O
credited O
twice O
in O
the O
' O
screenplay O
by O
' O
credits O
. O

Important O
cities O
along O
the O
coast O
include O
Odessa B-LOC
, O
Sevastopol B-LOC
, O
Samsun B-LOC
, O
and O
Istanbul B-LOC
. O

However O
, O
the O
player O
does O
not O
directly O
play O
as O
the O
game O
's O
protagonist O
as O
in O
most O
JRPGs B-MISC
, O
but O
rather O
, O
as O
a O
self-named O
" O
guardian O
spirit O
" O
that O
directly O
interacts O
with O
the O
protagonist O
through O
preset O
text O
dialogue O
tree O
response O
options O
. O

They O
also O
participated O
with O
the O
same O
team O
in O
the O
2004 B-MISC
Summer I-MISC
Olympics I-MISC
, O
but O
were O
eliminated O
in O
the O
series O
due O
to O
a O
mistake O
in O
an O
exchange O
. O

Polling O
conducted O
throughout O
March O
2009 O
by O
Maurice B-PER
de I-PER
Hond I-PER
indicated O
the O
Party B-ORG
for I-ORG
Freedom I-ORG
was O
the O
most O
popular O
parliamentary O
party O
. O

In O
line O
with O
this O
policy O
, O
several O
new O
parks O
, O
including O
the O
innovative O
Superkilen B-LOC
in O
the O
Nørrebro B-LOC
district O
, O
have O
been O
completed O
or O
are O
under O
development O
in O
areas O
lacking O
green O
spaces O
. O

On O
September O
13 O
, O
1965 O
he O
gave O
up O
Willie B-PER
Mays I-PER
' O
500th O
home O
run O
. O

He O
worked O
as O
a O
high O
school O
teacher O
in O
Honolulu B-LOC
from O
1953 O
until O
1960 O
, O
when O
he O
was O
then O
hired O
as O
a O
vice O
principal O
. O

However O
, O
in O
January O
2015 O
, O
the O
program O
was O
yet O
again O
tape-delayed O
to O
midnight O
in O
favor O
of O
" O
The B-MISC
Nightly I-MISC
Show I-MISC
with I-MISC
Larry I-MISC
Wilmore I-MISC
" O
. O

Manager O
Terry B-PER
Francona I-PER
expressed O
excitement O
over O
the O
prospect O
of O
playing O
a O
true O
center O
fielder O
in O
left O
field O
, O
creating O
a O
larger O
fielding O
range O
and O
more O
aggressive O
style O
. O

The O
VIC-20 B-MISC
version O
was O
released O
on O
cartridge O
, O
including O
the O
level O
editor O
. O

Given O
his O
chance O
by O
the O
injuries O
to O
other O
players O
, O
he O
became O
the O
linchpin O
of O
the O
England B-LOC
team O
in O
the O
1986 B-MISC
FIFA I-MISC
World I-MISC
Cup I-MISC
in O
Mexico B-LOC
. O

Louis B-PER
accordingly O
bolted O
the O
gates O
of O
Bourges B-LOC
against O
the O
new O
bishop O
. O

In O
1902 O
Bohuslav B-PER
Brauner I-PER
suggested O
that O
there O
was O
a O
then-unknown O
element O
with O
properties O
intermediate O
between O
those O
of O
the O
known O
elements O
neodymium O
( O
60 O
) O
and O
samarium O
( O
62 O
) O
; O
this O
was O
confirmed O
in O
1914 O
by O
Henry B-PER
Moseley I-PER
, O
who O
, O
having O
measured O
the O
atomic O
numbers O
of O
all O
the O
elements O
then O
known O
, O
found O
that O
atomic O
number O
61 O
was O
missing O
. O

The O
islands O
' O
many O
caves O
, O
such O
as O
those O
at O
Chalis B-LOC
Ek I-LOC
are O
nesting O
grounds O
for O
the O
edible-nest O
swiftlet O
, O
whose O
nests O
are O
prized O
in O
China B-LOC
for O
bird O
's O
nest O
soup O
. O

There O
were O
also O
various O
resistance O
movements O
around O
Otto B-PER
von I-PER
Habsburg I-PER
that O
pursued O
this O
goal O
. O

Appreciating O
travel O
in O
general O
, O
Jeeves B-PER
wants O
to O
go O
on O
a O
cruise O
in O
two O
different O
stories O
, O
" O
The B-MISC
Spot I-MISC
of I-MISC
Art I-MISC
" O
and O
" O
The B-MISC
Code I-MISC
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
Woosters I-MISC
" O
. O

Roy B-PER
Orbison I-PER
's O
song O
" O
Only B-MISC
the I-MISC
Lonely I-MISC
" O
is O
played O
in O
its O
entirety O
in O
the O
movie O
's O
opening O
scene O
. O

The O
two O
main O
religious O
groups O
are O
Christians B-MISC
and O
Muslims B-MISC
. O

One O
year O
later O
, O
he O
received O
his O
Master O
of O
Science O
at O
Columbia B-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

Sochi B-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
popular O
tourism O
centres O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
prominent O
financial O
centre O
in O
Russia B-LOC
. O

It O
is O
believed O
that O
it O
was O
here O
, O
on O
the O
11 O
November O
1918 O
, O
that O
Karl B-PER
Liebknecht I-PER
and O
Rosa B-PER
Luxemburg I-PER
's O
leftist O
revolutionary O
group O
renamed O
themselves O
the O
" O
Spartakusbund B-ORG
" O
( O
The O
Spartacus B-ORG
League I-ORG
) O
. O

In O
1943 O
, O
Tommy B-PER
Flowers I-PER
designed O
and O
built O
the O
Colossus B-MISC
, O
the O
world O
's O
first O
fully O
functional O
, O
electronic O
, O
digital O
and O
programmable O
computer O
. O

Over O
218,000 O
individuals O
are O
white O
; O
1,106 O
are O
of O
mixed O
race O
; O
2,215 O
are O
Asian O
" O
– O
mainly O
Bangladeshi B-LOC
( O
1,015 O
) O
; O
300 O
are O
black O
; O
and O
1,195 O
belong O
to O
other O
ethnic O
groups O
. O

Travis B-PER
' O
father O
had O
seen O
his O
mother O
as O
a O
Parisian B-MISC
, O
and O
this O
became O
" O
a O
sickness O
" O
. O

This O
method O
of O
execution O
was O
considered O
the O
most O
shameful O
and O
degrading O
in O
the O
Roman B-MISC
world O
, O
and O
advocates O
of O
the O
criterion O
claim O
this O
method O
of O
execution O
is O
therefore O
the O
least O
likely O
to O
have O
been O
invented O
by O
the O
followers O
of O
Jesus B-PER
. O

He O
retired O
as O
PR O
in-charge O
at O
the O
AIIMS B-LOC
, O
New B-LOC
Delhi I-LOC
. O

One O
of O
the O
oldest O
known O
board O
games O
is O
Senet B-MISC
, O
a O
game O
played O
in O
Ancient B-LOC
Egypt I-LOC
, O
enjoyed O
by O
the O
pharaoh O
Tutankhamun B-PER
. O

At O
the O
age O
of O
five O
, O
he O
was O
given O
his O
first O
pair O
of O
vibraphone O
mallets O
by O
Lionel B-PER
Hampton I-PER
. O

Sweeping O
is O
done O
for O
several O
reasons O
: O
to O
make O
the O
stone O
travel O
farther O
, O
to O
decrease O
the O
amount O
of O
curl O
, O
and O
to O
clean O
debris O
from O
the O
stone O
's O
path. O
Sweeping B-MISC
is O
able O
to O
make O
the O
stone O
travel O
farther O
and O
straighter O
by O
slightly O
melting O
the O
ice O
under O
the O
brooms O
, O
thus O
decreasing O
the O
friction O
as O
the O
stone O
travels O
across O
that O
part O
of O
the O
ice O
. O

" O
The O
angle O
I O
took O
on O
it O
was O
that O
it O
was O
n’t O
really O
acting O
" O
, O
said O
Björk B-PER
. O

when O
news O
broke O
of O
the O
bombing O
in O
Thessaloniki B-LOC
. O

The O
winter O
( O
November–December O
) O
2010 O
– O
( O
January–April O
) O
2011 O
was O
exceptionally O
extreme O
with O
snow O
depth O
reaching O
at O
least O
146 O
cm O
, O
2 O
inches O
short O
of O
5 O
feet O
( O
snowdrifts O
6 O
meters O
, O
almost O
20 O
feet O
) O
the O
highest O
in O
Northern B-LOC
Europe I-LOC
. O

He O
published O
advertisements O
in O
various O
newspapers O
like O
" O
Induprakash B-MISC
" O
calling O
for O
the O
cast O
and O
crew O
required O
for O
the O
film O
. O

Douglass B-PER
argued O
that O
white O
women O
, O
already O
empowered O
by O
their O
social O
connections O
to O
fathers O
, O
husbands O
, O
and O
brothers O
, O
at O
least O
vicariously O
had O
the O
vote O
. O

If O
the O
answer O
is O
" O
yes O
" O
, O
then O
" O
x O
" O
= O
TRUE O
, O
otherwise O
" O
x O
" O
= O
FALSE B-MISC
. O

The O
manufacturing O
plant O
in O
El B-LOC
Salheya I-LOC
employs O
c O
. O

After O
the O
suspension O
of O
Chennai B-ORG
Super I-ORG
Kings I-ORG
for O
2 O
years O
, O
he O
was O
bought O
by O
Gujarat B-ORG
Lions I-ORG
. O

An O
eruption O
in O
July O
2000 O
was O
seen O
from O
Chuquicamata B-LOC
, O
and O
the O
noise O
was O
audible O
as O
far O
as O
San B-LOC
Antonio I-LOC
de I-LOC
los I-LOC
Cobres I-LOC
, O
away O
. O

A O
few O
years O
later O
, O
resistance O
appeared O
in O
bacterial O
species O
not O
naturally O
producing O
AmpC O
enzymes O
( O
" O
K. O
pneumoniae O
" O
, O
" O
Salmonella B-PER
" O
spp. O
, O
" O
P. O
mirabilis O
" O
) O
due O
to O
the O
production O
of O
TEM O
- O
or O
SHV-type O
ESBLs O
( O
extended O
spectrum O
beta O
lactamases O
) O
. O

By O
the O
early O
18th O
century O
, O
the O
custom O
had O
become O
common O
in O
towns O
of O
the O
upper O
Rhineland B-LOC
, O
but O
it O
had O
not O
yet O
spread O
to O
rural O
areas O
. O

The O
main O
public O
transportation O
service O
is O
bus O
line O
23 O
, O
as O
well O
as O
train O
station O
Østbanetorvet B-LOC
. O

On O
12 O
March O
1942 O
, O
the O
company O
's O
founder O
, O
Robert B-PER
Bosch I-PER
, O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
80 O
. O

Also O
found O
here O
are O
600 O
inscriptions O
in O
fine O
calligraphy O
of O
writings O
in O
the O
Northern B-LOC
Wei I-LOC
style O
. O

Other O
songs O
include O
" O
Y.M.C.A. B-MISC
" O
( O
1979 O
) O
and O
" O
In B-MISC
the I-MISC
Navy I-MISC
" O
( O
1979 O
) O
. O

The O
collaboration O
was O
originally O
intended O
to O
be O
a O
remix O
of O
the O
song O
, O
while O
the O
solo O
version O
would O
have O
been O
included O
on O
Rihanna B-PER
's O
fifth O
studio O
album O
" O
Loud B-MISC
" O
. O

His O
run O
aggregate O
, O
1,018 O
, O
beat O
the O
record O
set O
by O
Rusi B-PER
Modi I-PER
in O
1944 O
– O
45 O
. O

The O
core O
storyline O
is O
loosely O
based O
on O
the O
1984 O
movie O
" O
Streets B-MISC
of I-MISC
Fire I-MISC
" O
. O

Poet O
and O
critic O
Walter B-PER
J. I-PER
Turner I-PER
commented O
in O
" O
The B-MISC
Spectator I-MISC
" O
, O
" O
This O
book O
alone O
, O
in O
my O
opinion O
, O
ranks O
him O
as O
a O
major O
poet O
" O
. O

As O
the O
South B-MISC
ran O
out O
of O
manpower O
the O
issue O
of O
arming O
the O
slaves O
became O
paramount O
. O

The O
NICE B-ORG
also O
recommends O
offering O
CBT O
to O
people O
suffering O
from O
schizophrenia O
, O
as O
well O
as O
those O
at O
risk O
of O
suffering O
from O
a O
psychotic O
episode O
. O

By O
1935 O
the O
Blueshirts B-ORG
had O
disintegrated O
. O

The O
coup O
brought O
Sankara B-PER
to O
power O
and O
his O
government O
began O
to O
implement O
a O
series O
of O
revolutionary O
programs O
which O
included O
mass-vaccinations O
, O
infrastructure O
improvements O
, O
the O
expansion O
of O
women O
's O
rights O
, O
encouragement O
of O
domestic O
agricultural O
consumption O
and O
anti-desertification O
projects O
. O

The O
remaining O
development O
of O
the O
tree O
greatly O
depends O
on O
the O
climate O
, O
soil O
quality O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
cultivation O
and O
how O
the O
trees O
are O
tended O
by O
the O
Christmas B-MISC
tree B-MISC
farmer O
. O

He O
was O
far O
from O
sympathizing O
with O
the O
Burgundians B-MISC
. O

Richard B-PER
Arkwright I-PER
built O
his O
cotton O
mills O
at O
the O
start O
of O
the O
Industrial I-MISC
Revolution I-MISC
. O

In O
1972 O
, O
he O
tried O
his O
luck O
in O
Brazil B-LOC
for O
a O
second O
time O
, O
but O
returned O
to O
Nacional B-ORG
in O
Uruguay B-LOC
after O
only O
one O
season O
at O
Fluminense B-ORG
. O

He O
is O
godfather O
to O
Mitchell B-PER
Robinson I-PER
. O

Upon O
reaching O
Bordeaux B-LOC
, O
he O
left O
them O
in O
the O
charge O
of O
the O
archbishop O
of O
Bordeaux B-LOC
, O
one O
of O
his O
few O
loyal O
vassals O
. O

The O
Sierra B-LOC
Morena I-LOC
, O
due O
to O
its O
morphology O
and O
the O
acidic O
content O
of O
its O
rocks O
, O
developed O
principally O
relatively O
poor O
, O
shallow O
soils O
, O
suitable O
only O
for O
forests O
. O

Before O
the O
creation O
of O
United B-ORG
Artists I-ORG
, O
Chaplin B-PER
married O
for O
the O
first O
time O
. O

A O
vast O
majority O
of O
the O
caves O
were O
carved O
in O
the O
second O
period O
, O
wherein O
a O
shrine O
or O
sanctuary O
is O
appended O
at O
the O
rear O
of O
the O
cave O
, O
centred O
on O
a O
large O
statue O
of O
the O
Buddha B-PER
, O
along O
with O
exuberantly O
detailed O
reliefs O
and O
deities O
near O
him O
as O
well O
as O
on O
the O
pillars O
and O
walls O
, O
all O
carved O
out O
of O
the O
natural O
rock O
. O

Chris B-PER
Martin I-PER
once O
proclaimed O
the O
band O
's O
music O
as O
" O
limestone O
rock O
" O
in O
comparison O
to O
" O
hard O
rock O
" O
. O

Godzilla B-MISC
fights O
Ebirah B-MISC
, O
but O
the O
huge O
crustacean O
escapes O
. O

Electoral O
systems O
with O
election O
of O
just O
one O
winner O
in O
each O
district O
( O
i.e. O
, O
" O
winner-takes-all O
" O
electoral O
systems O
) O
and O
no O
proportional O
distribution O
of O
extra O
mandates O
to O
smaller O
parties O
tend O
to O
create O
two-party O
systems O
( O
Duverger B-PER
's O
law O
) O
. O

Although O
her O
native O
tongue O
was O
Poitevin B-MISC
, O
she O
was O
taught O
to O
read O
and O
speak O
Latin B-MISC
, O
was O
well O
versed O
in O
music O
and O
literature O
, O
and O
schooled O
in O
riding O
, O
hawking O
, O
and O
hunting O
. O

It O
was O
formed O
by O
people O
who O
left O
Cornwall B-LOC
's O
main O
nationalist O
party O
Mebyon B-ORG
Kernow I-ORG
on O
28 O
May O
1975 O
, O
but O
it O
is O
no O
longer O
for O
independence O
. O

This O
expression O
becomes O
, O
via O
some O
steps O
, O
the O
Gibbs B-PER
free O
energy O
equation O
for O
reactants O
and O
products O
in O
the O
system O
: O
Δ O
" O
G O
" O
[ O
the O
Gibbs B-PER
free O
energy O
change O
of O
the O
system O
] O
= O
Δ O
" O
H O
" O
[ O
the O
enthalpy O
change O
] O
− O
" O
T O
" O
Δ O
" O
S O
" O
[ O
the O
entropy O
change O
] O
. O

In O
1946 O
, O
he O
recorded O
his O
first O
records O
for O
Columbia B-ORG
Records I-ORG
and O
then O
for O
Aristocrat B-ORG
Records I-ORG
, O
a O
newly O
formed O
label O
run O
by O
the O
brothers O
Leonard B-PER
and O
Phil B-PER
Chess I-PER
. O

A O
" O
high O
commission O
" O
is O
an O
embassy O
of O
a O
Commonwealth B-ORG
country O
located O
in O
another O
Commonwealth B-ORG
country O
. O

It O
is O
also O
frequently O
serviced O
by O
Ingham B-LOC
and O
the O
nearby O
town O
of O
Halifax B-LOC
. O

The O
society O
also O
has O
an O
expansive O
archive O
on O
framer O
of O
the O
U.S. B-LOC
constitution O
John B-PER
Dickinson I-PER
. O

Frasier B-MISC
Crane I-MISC
started O
as O
a O
recurring O
character O
and O
became O
a O
permanent O
one O
. O

After O
missing O
the O
2010 B-MISC
FIFA I-MISC
World I-MISC
Cup I-MISC
due O
to O
a O
hernia O
, O
and O
six O
against O
France B-LOC
( O
2 O
– O
0 O
, O
quarterfinals O
) O
for O
the O
eventual O
champions O
. O

The O
key O
match O
was O
their O
nine-run O
defeat O
by O
Surrey B-ORG
at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC
in O
late O
August O
which O
, O
subject O
to O
Warwickshire B-LOC
winning O
their O
final O
match O
, O
decided O
the O
outcome O
. O

The O
precise O
meaning O
of O
a O
term O
given O
by O
a O
mathematical O
definition O
is O
often O
different O
than O
the O
English B-MISC
definition O
of O
the O
word O
used O
, O
which O
can O
lead O
to O
confusion O
, O
particularly O
when O
the O
meanings O
are O
close O
. O

The O
game O
itself O
is O
very O
reminiscent O
to O
" O
Indiana B-MISC
Jones I-MISC
and I-MISC
the I-MISC
Temple I-MISC
of I-MISC
Doom I-MISC
" O
. O

The O
seaway O
locks O
permit O
passage O
of O
a O
ship O
long O
by O
feet O
wide O
( O
the O
Seawaymax B-LOC
limit O
) O
. O

Another O
visit O
through O
the O
area O
in O
1529 O
reinforced O
these O
ideas O
, O
but O
he O
was O
captured O
and O
burned O
at O
the O
stake O
in O
Klausen B-LOC
on O
September O
6 O
, O
1529 O
. O

He O
guest-starred O
as O
one O
half O
of O
a O
con O
artist O
couple O
alongside O
Jennifer B-PER
Finnigan I-PER
in O
a O
sixth-season O
episode O
of O
USA B-LOC
's O
" O
Psych B-MISC
" O
and O
also O
appeared O
in O
the O
music O
video O
" O
Boys B-MISC
" O
by O
Britney B-PER
Spears I-PER
. O

As O
of O
2017 O
, O
the O
official O
population O
of O
Catalonia B-LOC
was O
7,522,596 O
. O

The O
Plinian B-LOC
deposit O
has O
a O
colour O
ranging O
from O
white O
to O
creamy O
. O

The O
word O
‘ O
rapt O
’ O
, O
showing O
how O
Macbeth B-PER
is O
obsessed O
with O
the O
witches O
’ O
powers O
and O
is O
tempted O
by O
their O
predictions O
. O

Several O
significant O
Jacobite B-ORG
units O
were O
still O
" O
en O
route O
" O
or O
engaged O
far O
to O
the O
north O
, O
but O
on O
learning O
of O
the O
government O
advance O
their O
main O
army O
of O
about O
5,400 O
left O
its O
base O
at O
Inverness B-LOC
on O
15 O
April O
and O
assembled O
in O
battle O
order O
5 O
" O
miles O
( O
8 O
" O
km O
) O
to O
the O
east O
. O

Many O
indigenous O
people O
left O
their O
traditional O
villages O
and O
sought O
to O
be O
counted O
as O
mestizos O
to O
avoid O
tribute O
payments O
to O
the O
Spanish B-MISC
. O

Ideas O
developed O
by O
Charles B-PER
Darwin I-PER
has O
ethnocentric O
ideals O
where O
societies O
who O
believed O
they O
were O
superior O
were O
most O
likely O
to O
survive O
and O
prosper O
. O

The O
software O
's O
" O
automation O
of O
recurring O
financial O
processes O
" O
adds O
" O
visibility O
and O
transparency O
" O
and O
strengthens O
" O
internal O
controls O
and O
compliance O
documentation O
" O
of O
data O
maintained O
by O
SAP B-ORG
. O

A O
correspondent O
not O
seen O
on O
camera O
will O
ask O
pedestrians O
on O
Hollywood B-LOC
Boulevard I-LOC
a O
fake O
question O
related O
to O
an O
actual O
current O
news O
event O
. O

The O
" O
Études B-MISC
" O
( O
1915 O
) O
for O
piano O
have O
divided O
opinion O
. O

While O
riding O
near O
London B-LOC
, O
a O
fit O
of O
melancholy O
seized O
him O
on O
the O
road O
; O
he O
alighted O
, O
giving O
the O
horse O
to O
the O
servant O
. O

He O
finished O
his O
18-year O
career O
with O
Krefeld B-ORG
Pinguine I-ORG
of O
the O
Deutsche B-ORG
Eishockey I-ORG
Liga I-ORG
in O
Germany B-LOC
. O

Next O
season O
he O
was O
a O
regular O
again O
as O
Ajax B-ORG
reached O
the O
quarter-finals O
of O
the O
UEFA B-MISC
Champions I-MISC
League I-MISC
. O

Populations O
from O
northern O
Chile B-LOC
with O
very O
stout O
stems O
up O
to O
3.5 O
" O
cm O
diameter O
have O
sometimes O
been O
treated O
as O
a O
separate O
species O
" O
Equisetum O
xylochaetum O
" O
, O
but O
this O
is O
not O
widely O
regarded O
as O
distinct O
. O

12 O
( O
1829 O
) O
and O
Op B-MISC
. O

" O
Stir O
frying O
" O
( O
) O
is O
a O
Chinese B-MISC
cooking O
technique O
in O
which O
ingredients O
are O
fried O
in O
a O
small O
amount O
of O
very O
hot O
oil O
while O
being O
stirred O
in O
a O
wok O
. O

Hexagonal O
BN O
was O
first O
used O
in O
cosmetics O
around O
1940 O
in O
Japan B-LOC
. O

The O
Finnish B-MISC
ablative O
is O
also O
used O
in O
time O
expressions O
to O
indicate O
times O
of O
something O
happening O
( O
" O
kymmeneltä O
" O
" O
at O
ten O
" O
) O
as O
well O
as O
with O
verbs O
expressing O
feelings O
or O
emotions O
. O

It O
stars O
Jennifer B-PER
Jason I-PER
Leigh I-PER
and O
Jason B-PER
Patric I-PER
as O
two O
cops O
in O
the O
1970 O
s O
who O
go O
undercover O
on O
a O
case O
. O

Initially O
, O
guitarist O
David B-PER
O'List I-PER
( O
from O
The B-ORG
Nice I-ORG
) O
was O
part O
of O
the O
group O
, O
but O
he O
was O
replaced O
by O
Phil B-PER
Manzanera I-PER
in O
February O
1972 O
, O
just O
as O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
was O
about O
to O
be O
recorded O
. O

It O
was O
Iran B-LOC
’s O
gateway O
to O
Russia B-LOC
and O
Europe B-LOC
; O
therefore O
it O
was O
influenced O
by O
western O
architecture O
. O

The O
Corporation B-ORG
owns O
Old B-LOC
Spitalfields I-LOC
Market I-LOC
and O
Billingsgate B-LOC
Fish I-LOC
Market I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
neighbouring O
London B-LOC
Borough I-LOC
of I-LOC
Tower I-LOC
Hamlets I-LOC
. O

It O
was O
originally O
released O
for O
the O
Amiga B-MISC
, O
but O
later O
ported O
to O
MS-DOS B-MISC
, O
as O
well O
as O
released O
in O
distinctly O
different O
forms O
to O
consoles O
. O

He O
soon O
became O
disillusioned O
with O
the O
work O
and O
in O
1950 O
applied O
for O
a O
job O
as O
a O
radio O
talk O
producer O
with O
the O
BBC B-ORG
. O

A O
special O
position O
is O
held O
by O
the O
autochthonous O
and O
geographically O
dispersed O
Roma B-MISC
ethnic O
community O
. O

The O
task O
was O
passed O
to O
Boris B-PER
Yeltsin I-PER
, O
chair O
of O
the O
local O
party O
, O
who O
had O
the O
house O
demolished O
in O
September O
1977 O
. O

She O
also O
directed O
" O
The B-MISC
Safety I-MISC
of I-MISC
Objects I-MISC
" O
( O
2001 O
) O
, O
which O
was O
adapted O
from O
the O
short O
stories O
of O
A. B-PER
M. I-PER
Homes I-PER
and O
focused O
on O
heterosexual O
love O
in O
suburbia O
. O

In O
addition O
to O
capturing O
the O
regular O
ghosts O
in O
the O
mansion O
, O
Luigi B-MISC
must O
also O
draw O
out O
special O
" O
portrait O
ghosts O
" O
from O
some O
rooms O
, O
each O
requiring O
a O
condition O
be O
met O
to O
make O
them O
available O
for O
capture O
. O

Small O
Jewish B-MISC
and O
Hindu B-MISC
minorities O
are O
also O
present O
in O
the O
city O
. O

The O
first O
recorded O
English B-MISC
visitor O
was O
Sir O
Francis B-PER
Drake I-PER
in O
1586 O
, O
who O
reported O
that O
the O
" O
caymanas O
" O
were O
edible O
, O
but O
it O
was O
the O
turtles O
which O
attracted O
ships O
in O
search O
of O
fresh O
meat O
for O
their O
crews O
. O

Seven O
years O
later O
Walthari B-PER
died O
, O
giving O
Audoin B-PER
the O
opportunity O
to O
crown O
himself O
and O
overthrow O
the O
reigning O
Lethings B-PER
. O

The O
classics O
examination O
was O
revised O
in O
1344 O
, O
under O
the O
reign O
of O
Chunghye B-PER
, O
on O
the O
model O
of O
the O
examination O
system O
then O
employed O
in O
Yuan B-LOC
Dynasty I-LOC
. O

Charleston B-LOC
became O
a O
hotspot O
for O
pirates O
from O
the O
1670 O
s O
; O
the O
combination O
of O
a O
weak O
government O
and O
corruption O
made O
the O
city O
popular O
with O
pirates O
, O
who O
frequently O
visited O
and O
raided O
the O
city O
. O

She O
worked O
as O
the O
basketball O
development O
officer O
/ O
assistant O
coach O
for O
the O
South B-ORG
Dragons I-ORG
in O
the O
Australian B-ORG
National I-ORG
Basketball I-ORG
League I-ORG
. O

As O
mentioned O
above O
, O
the O
NSA B-ORG
announced O
in O
2015 O
that O
it O
plans O
to O
transition O
to O
quantum-resistant O
algorithms O
. O

BC O
) O
and O
Caesar B-PER
( O
mid-1 O
st O
c O
. O

By O
contrast O
, O
the O
Arabic B-MISC
and O
Hebrew B-MISC
scripts O
sometimes O
perform O
the O
role O
of O
true O
alphabets O
rather O
than O
abjads O
when O
used O
to O
write O
certain O
Indo-European B-MISC
languages O
, O
including O
Kurdish B-MISC
, O
Bosnian B-MISC
, O
and O
Yiddish B-MISC
. O

Artin B-PER
reformulated O
the O
reciprocity O
laws O
as O
a O
statement O
that O
the O
Artin B-PER
symbol O
from O
ideals O
( O
or O
ideles O
) O
to O
elements O
of O
a O
Galois B-PER
group O
is O
trivial O
on O
a O
certain O
subgroup O
. O

The O
principal O
part O
is O
the O
" O
Sandhyopāsanā O
mantram O
" O
( O
सन्ध्योपासना O
मन्त्रम् O
) O
, O
which O
involves O
contemplation O
on O
Brahman B-PER
, O
referred O
as O
' O
Brahmabhāvanam O
' O
. O

Her O
monograph O
" O
Intention B-MISC
" O
is O
generally O
recognised O
as O
her O
greatest O
and O
most O
influential O
work O
, O
and O
the O
continuing O
philosophical O
interest O
in O
the O
concepts O
of O
intention O
, O
action O
, O
and O
practical O
reasoning O
can O
be O
said O
to O
have O
taken O
its O
main O
impetus O
from O
this O
work O
. O

A O
scene O
from O
the O
film O
was O
used O
in O
the O
1971 O
film O
" O
The B-MISC
Hellstrom I-MISC
Chronicle I-MISC
" O
. O

Pink B-ORG
Floyd I-ORG
recorded O
several O
tributes O
and O
homages O
to O
him O
, O
including O
the O
1975 O
song O
suite O
" O
Shine B-MISC
On I-MISC
You I-MISC
Crazy I-MISC
Diamond I-MISC
" O
and O
the O
1979 O
rock O
opera O
" O
The B-MISC
Wall I-MISC
" O
. O

Assistive O
technology O
devices O
have O
been O
created O
to O
enable O
people O
with O
disabilities O
to O
use O
modern O
touch O
screen O
mobile O
computers O
such O
as O
the O
iPad B-MISC
, O
iPhone B-MISC
and O
iPod B-MISC
touch I-MISC
. O

This O
permutation O
group O
is O
isomorphic O
, O
as O
an O
abstract O
group O
, O
to O
the O
Klein B-PER
group O
" O
V O
" O
. O

They O
were O
four-time O
consecutive O
World B-MISC
silver O
medalists O
from O
1985 O
to O
1988 O
. O

Control O
of O
proapoptotic O
proteins O
under O
normal O
cell O
conditions O
of O
nonapoptotic O
cells O
is O
incompletely O
understood O
, O
but O
in O
general O
, O
Bax B-MISC
or O
Bak B-MISC
are O
activated O
by O
the O
activation O
of O
BH3 O
- O
only O
proteins O
, O
part O
of O
the O
Bcl-2 O
family O
. O

Philip B-PER
deliberately O
commanded O
his O
troops O
to O
retreat O
, O
counting O
on O
the O
untested O
Athenian B-MISC
hoplites O
to O
follow O
, O
thus O
breaking O
their O
line O
. O

According O
to O
singer O
Peter B-PER
Cetera I-PER
, O
he O
originally O
wrote O
his O
best-selling O
solo O
single O
" O
Glory B-MISC
of I-MISC
Love I-MISC
" O
as O
the O
end O
title O
for O
this O
film O
, O
but O
was O
passed O
over O
by O
United B-ORG
Artists I-ORG
, O
and O
instead O
used O
the O
theme O
for O
" O
The B-MISC
Karate I-MISC
Kid I-MISC
Part I-MISC
II I-MISC
" O
. O

The O
work O
is O
now O
viewed O
as O
a O
more O
general O
argument O
against O
absolute O
monarchy O
( O
particularly O
as O
espoused O
by O
Robert B-PER
Filmer I-PER
and O
Thomas B-PER
Hobbes I-PER
) O
and O
for O
individual O
consent O
as O
the O
basis O
of O
political O
legitimacy O
. O

Today O
the O
dialect O
is O
heard O
only O
rarely O
in O
the O
Upper B-LOC
Harz I-LOC
in O
everyday O
life O
and O
it O
is O
mainly O
members O
of O
the O
older O
generations O
who O
still O
use O
it O
, O
so O
occasional O
articles O
in O
the O
local O
papers O
are O
printed O
in O
" O
Upper B-LOC
Harz I-LOC
" O
, O
which O
helps O
to O
preserve O
it O
. O

There O
are O
various O
Afghan B-MISC
tribes O
, O
and O
an O
estimated O
2 O
– O
3 O
" O
million O
nomads O
. O

In O
2008 O
, O
the O
city O
was O
listed O
by O
Lonely B-ORG
Planet I-ORG
as O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
top O
10 O
tourist O
cities O
. O

Waltz O
began O
as O
a O
country O
folk O
dance O
in O
Austria B-LOC
and O
Bavaria B-LOC
in O
the O
17th O
century O
. O

He O
later O
briefly O
served O
as O
president O
of O
a O
mining O
company O
in O
West B-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
. O

Having O
rejected O
conventional O
medical O
treatment O
, O
he O
credited O
his O
survival O
to O
the O
adoption O
of O
a O
macrobiotic O
diet O
recommended O
to O
him O
by O
actress O
Gloria B-PER
Swanson I-PER
. O

In O
the O
last O
and O
highest O
section O
, O
the O
Theodul B-LOC
Pass I-LOC
must O
be O
crossed O
before O
returning O
to O
Zermatt B-LOC
. O

On O
October O
19 O
, O
1966 O
, O
NBC B-ORG
signed O
a O
three-year O
contract O
with O
Major B-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
. O

Although O
obrajes O
in O
Brihuega B-LOC
were O
small-scale O
enterprises O
, O
quite O
a O
number O
of O
them O
in O
Puebla B-LOC
employed O
up O
to O
100 O
workers O
. O

Telegraphs O
employing O
electrostatic O
attraction O
were O
the O
basis O
of O
early O
experiments O
in O
electrical O
telegraphy O
in O
Europe B-LOC
, O
but O
were O
abandoned O
as O
being O
impractical O
and O
were O
never O
developed O
into O
a O
useful O
communication O
system O
. O

Dixie B-PER
Dean I-PER
said O
that O
he O
was O
the O
best O
crosser O
of O
the O
ball O
that O
he O
played O
with O
. O

The O
US B-LOC
dollar O
was O
and O
remains O
legal O
tender O
( O
used O
as O
currency O
) O
. O

Per O
Article O
11 O
, O
Section O
1 O
, O
of O
the O
Constitution B-MISC
of I-MISC
California I-MISC
, O
they O
are O
the O
legal O
subdivisions O
of O
the O
state O
. O

( O
William B-PER
Blackstone I-PER
's O
" O
Commentaries B-MISC
on I-MISC
the I-MISC
Laws I-MISC
of I-MISC
England I-MISC
" O
) O
. O

Ten O
years O
later O
he O
returned O
to O
Formula B-MISC
One I-MISC
for O
the O
final O
two O
races O
of O
the O
1992 O
season O
. O

The O
angels O
blowing O
trumpets O
are O
all O
in O
one O
group O
, O
whereas O
in O
the O
Book B-MISC
of I-MISC
Revelation I-MISC
they O
are O
sent O
to O
" O
the O
four O
corners O
of O
the O
earth O
" O
. O

Only O
five O
of O
Aristotle B-PER
's O
works O
had O
all O
three O
types O
of O
commentaries O
: O
" O
Physics B-MISC
" O
, O
" O
Metaphysics O
" O
, O
" O
On B-MISC
the I-MISC
Soul I-MISC
" O
, O
" O
On B-MISC
the I-MISC
Heavens I-MISC
" O
, O
and O
" O
Posterior B-MISC
Analytics I-MISC
" O
. O

Charles B-PER
met O
Carloman B-PER
, O
but O
Carloman B-PER
refused O
to O
participate O
and O
returned O
to O
Burgundy B-LOC
. O

He O
was O
head O
coach O
with O
the O
Golden B-ORG
State I-ORG
Warriors I-ORG
from O
1999 O
to O
2001 O
, O
a O
tenure O
of O
105 O
games O
. O

" O
It O
was O
Marmik B-MISC
issue O
on O
5 O
June O
1966 O
which O
first O
announced O
the O
launch O
of O
membership O
for O
the O
Shiv B-ORG
Sena I-ORG
. O

Together O
with O
Allan B-PER
Caidic I-PER
, O
he O
shares O
the O
record O
of O
seeing O
action O
for O
the O
Asian B-MISC
Games I-MISC
four O
consecutive O
times O
in O
1986 O
, O
1990 O
, O
1994 O
and O
1998 O
. O

Jennifer B-PER
Lawrence I-PER
is O
attached O
to O
star O
in O
the O
lead O
role O
. O

Registered O
taxis O
in O
Casablanca B-LOC
are O
coloured O
red O
and O
known O
as O
" O
petit O
taxis O
" O
( O
small O
taxis O
) O
, O
or O
coloured O
white O
and O
known O
as O
" O
grands O
taxis O
" O
( O
big O
taxis O
) O
. O

The O
team O
ended O
the O
year O
as O
the O
number O
one O
team O
, O
winning O
the O
year-end O
championships O
over O
Katarina B-PER
Srebotnik I-PER
and O
Ai B-PER
Sugiyama I-PER
5 O
– O
7 O
, O
6 O
– O
3 O
, O
[ O
10 O
– O
8 O
] O
. O

He O
was O
unable O
to O
organize O
his O
writing O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
his O
life O
, O
so O
he O
asked O
A. B-PER
E. I-PER
Hotchner I-PER
to O
travel O
to O
Cuba B-LOC
to O
help O
him O
. O

The O
shaft O
of O
the O
Doric B-PER
order O
is O
channeled O
with O
20 O
flutes O
. O

The O
twins O
have O
credited O
the O
film O
" O
Ghostbusters B-MISC
" O
and O
the O
cartoon O
series O
" O
Scooby-Doo B-MISC
" O
for O
influencing O
the O
game O
. O

On O
29 O
October O
, O
he O
scored O
the O
winning O
goal O
against O
his O
former O
team O
, O
Napoli B-ORG
, O
but O
did O
not O
celebrate O
his O
goal O
, O
in O
a O
2 O
– O
1 O
home O
win O
. O

While O
she O
did O
n't O
find O
her O
photograph O
, O
nearly O
100 O
original O
Ansel B-PER
Adams I-PER
photographs O
were O
discovered O
scattered O
across O
campus O
. O

He O
was O
being O
told O
to O
cross O
the O
Oxus B-LOC
and O
claim O
throne O
for O
Amir B-PER
. O

The O
river O
's O
total O
length O
is O
, O
of O
which O
are O
in O
Massachusetts B-LOC
. O

In O
1990 O
, O
he O
worked O
for O
the O
Toledo B-ORG
Mud I-ORG
Hens I-ORG
. O

He O
had O
also O
been O
a O
member O
of O
the O
League B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
South I-ORG
. O

At O
the O
end O
of O
the O
1996 O
collegiate O
season O
, O
UConn B-ORG
changed O
its O
head O
coaches O
and O
the O
new O
coach O
brought O
in O
an O
entirely O
new O
cadre O
of O
assistants O
. O

The O
game O
became O
the O
highest-selling O
Working B-ORG
Designs I-ORG
title O
to O
date O
, O
and O
the O
third O
highest-selling O
role-playing O
game O
of O
1999 O
behind O
" O
Final B-MISC
Fantasy I-MISC
VIII I-MISC
" O
and O
" O
Planescape B-MISC
: I-MISC
Torment I-MISC
" O
. O

The O
third O
, O
the O
cycle O
of O
the O
love O
, O
consisted O
of O
" O
Nemesis B-MISC
" O
. O

He O
found O
one O
Dries B-PER
van I-PER
Noten I-PER
tie O
he O
wore O
during O
the O
film O
to O
his O
liking O
and O
kept O
it O
. O

He O
learned O
to O
speak O
Turkish B-MISC
. O

However O
the O
season O
with O
Grenoble B-ORG
was O
reflected O
poorly O
as O
the O
team O
finished O
bottom O
of O
Ligue B-MISC
1 I-MISC
and O
was O
relegated O
. O

The O
consequence O
of O
excess O
and O
crowds O
can O
produce O
breaches O
of O
social O
norms O
of O
behaviour O
, O
sometimes O
causing O
injury O
or O
even O
death O
, O
such O
as O
for O
example O
, O
at O
the O
Altamont B-MISC
Free I-MISC
Concert I-MISC
, O
an O
outdoor O
rock O
festival O
. O

As O
a O
result O
, O
populations O
of O
47 O
threatened O
species O
increased O
, O
including O
the O
critically O
endangered O
Yangtze B-LOC
alligator O
. O

In O
2005 O
, O
he O
suffered O
a O
wrist O
injury O
on O
June O
17 O
while O
diving O
into O
first O
base O
during O
a O
game O
against O
the O
Twins B-ORG
. O

Many O
of O
the O
migrants O
came O
from O
the O
rural O
parts O
of O
west O
Wales B-LOC
which O
had O
been O
affected O
by O
an O
agricultural O
depression O
. O

He O
played O
a O
few O
games O
for O
the O
Hanshin B-ORG
Tigers I-ORG
in O
Japan B-LOC
( O
1997 O
) O
, O
before O
retiring O
. O

She O
also O
worked O
closely O
with O
the O
director O
George B-PER
Lucas I-PER
on O
her O
character O
's O
accent O
and O
mannerisms O
, O
and O
watched O
the O
films O
of O
Lauren B-PER
Bacall I-PER
, O
Audrey B-PER
Hepburn I-PER
, O
and O
Katharine B-PER
Hepburn I-PER
to O
draw O
inspiration O
from O
their O
voice O
and O
stature O
. O

Digital B-ORG
Equipment I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
invented O
a O
convention O
which O
used O
19 O
( O
the O
device O
control O
3 O
character O
( O
DC3 O
) O
, O
also O
known O
as O
control-S O
, O
or O
XOFF B-MISC
) O
to O
" O
S O
" O
top O
transmission O
, O
and O
17 O
( O
the O
device O
control O
1 O
character O
( O
DC1 O
) O
, O
a.k.a. O
control-Q O
, O
or O
XON O
) O
to O
start O
transmission O
. O

The O
third O
population O
, O
the O
western O
North B-LOC
Atlantic I-LOC
population O
, O
is O
the O
only O
population O
currently O
recognized O
in O
the O
North B-LOC
Atlantic I-LOC
. O

Beryllium B-LOC
has O
a O
large O
scattering O
cross O
section O
for O
high-energy O
neutrons O
, O
about O
6 O
barns O
for O
energies O
above O
approximately O
10 O
" O
keV O
. O

Moments O
later O
, O
Jerzy B-PER
Dudek I-PER
saved O
Andriy B-PER
Shevchenko I-PER
's O
penalty O
to O
win O
both O
the O
shoot-out O
and O
the O
final O
for O
Liverpool B-ORG
. O

There O
he O
worked O
with O
several O
firms O
, O
most O
recently O
including O
the O
well-known O
Venable B-ORG
LLP I-ORG
. O

By O
the O
end O
of O
the O
year O
, O
he O
took O
Jorge B-PER
Julio I-PER
's O
job O
as O
the O
closer O
. O

The O
natural O
abundance O
of O
hydrogen O
( O
H O
) O
in O
the O
Earth B-MISC
's O
atmosphere O
is O
only O
of O
the O
order O
of O
parts O
per O
million O
, O
but O
H O
is O
the O
most O
abundant O
diatomic O
molecule O
in O
the O
universe O
. O

He O
played O
in O
46 O
games O
for O
the O
1996 O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Yankees I-ORG
. O

Lucifer B-PER
, O
enraged O
at O
the O
spread O
of O
Jesus B-PER
's O
kingdom O
, O
convokes O
the O
fiends O
in O
council O
, O
and O
resolves O
to O
set O
up O
the O
pope O
as O
antichrist O
. O

In O
2013 O
, O
she O
rose O
to O
international O
prominence O
as O
co-host O
of O
BET B-ORG
's O
" O
106 B-MISC
& I-MISC
Park I-MISC
" O
. O

Apollo B-PER
is O
an O
important O
pastoral O
deity O
, O
and O
was O
the O
patron O
of O
herdsmen O
and O
shepherds O
. O

In O
recent O
years O
, O
the O
title O
has O
been O
used O
several O
times O
: O
for O
a O
song O
on O
Rob B-PER
Zombie I-PER
's O
1998 O
debut O
solo O
album O
, O
" O
Hellbilly B-MISC
Deluxe I-MISC
; O
" O
for O
a O
TV O
movie O
in O
2001 O
; O
for O
the O
name O
of O
the O
2004 O
album O
by O
The B-ORG
Cramps I-ORG
; O
for O
a O
documentary O
on O
special O
make-up O
effects O
applications O
in O
2005 O
; O
and O
for O
an O
8-minute O
short O
film O
in O
2011 O
. O

Newton B-PER
had O
himself O
made O
a O
justice O
of O
the O
peace O
in O
all O
the O
home O
counties O
. O

In O
2008 O
, O
two O
new O
species O
were O
discovered O
in O
Cameroon B-LOC
. O

On O
26 O
September O
, O
he O
debuted O
against O
Bangladesh B-LOC
. O

In O
Japan B-LOC
, O
printed O
parts O
are O
not O
used O
during O
lessons O
. O

On O
23 O
July O
, O
riots O
erupted O
in O
Edinburgh B-LOC
upon O
the O
first O
Sunday O
of O
the O
prayer O
book O
's O
usage O
, O
and O
unrest O
spread O
throughout O
the O
Kirk B-LOC
. O

It O
sits O
on O
the O
Chalus B-LOC
River I-LOC
by O
the O
Caspian B-LOC
. O

He O
introduced O
Bank B-ORG
regulations O
, O
simplified O
and O
reduced O
the O
corporate O
tax O
. O

The O
city O
was O
ruled O
shortly O
thereafter O
by O
Marwanids B-LOC
. O

The O
heads O
were O
carved O
from O
single O
blocks O
or O
boulders O
of O
volcanic O
basalt O
, O
found O
in O
the O
Sierra B-LOC
de I-LOC
los I-LOC
Tuxtlas I-LOC
. O

Based O
on O
the O
3GPP2 B-MISC
technical O
specification O
published O
on O
18 O
May O
2007 O
. O

In O
1999 O
he O
was O
appointed O
Regent O
of O
the O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
California I-ORG
by O
Governor O
Gray B-PER
Davis I-PER
until O
he O
resigned O
for O
unknown O
reasons O
in O
2007 O
. O

In O
the O
18th O
century O
, O
Voltaire B-PER
was O
a O
deist O
and O
was O
strongly O
critical O
of O
religious O
intolerance O
. O

Both O
groups O
interpolated O
the O
signature O
funk O
grooves O
of O
Parliament-Funkadelic B-ORG
. O

Spreading O
began O
opening O
the O
Labrador B-LOC
Sea I-LOC
around O
61 O
million O
years O
ago O
, O
continuing O
until O
36 O
million O
years O
ago O
. O

Often O
Picasso B-PER
's O
self-portraits O
depicted O
and O
revealed O
complicated O
psychological O
insights O
, O
both O
personal O
and O
profound O
about O
the O
inner O
state O
and O
well O
being O
of O
the O
artist O
. O

Total O
cement O
capacity O
worldwide O
was O
recorded O
at O
5245 O
Mt O
in O
2012 O
, O
with O
2950 O
Mt O
located O
in O
China B-LOC
and O
2295 O
Mt O
in O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
world O
. O

In O
1999 O
, O
the O
memoir O
was O
adapted O
into O
a O
film O
of O
the O
same O
name O
starring O
Winona B-PER
Ryder I-PER
, O
Angelina B-PER
Jolie I-PER
and O
Brittany B-PER
Murphy I-PER
. O

He O
usually O
read O
and O
responded O
to O
viewer O
e-mail O
and O
( O
since O
February O
2010 O
) O
Twitter B-MISC
messages O
for O
random O
responses O
to O
viewer O
questions O
. O

He O
was O
traded O
to O
the O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Rangers I-ORG
after O
the O
1995 O
season O
. O

In O
9.5 O
Confucius B-PER
says O
that O
a O
person O
may O
know O
the O
movements O
of O
the O
Tian B-PER
, O
and O
this O
provides O
with O
the O
sense O
of O
having O
a O
special O
place O
in O
the O
universe O
. O

Finally O
, O
in O
1988 O
, O
the O
NFL B-ORG
switched O
to O
the O
high-school O
and O
college O
football O
convention O
: O
the O
referee O
wears O
a O
white O
hat O
( O
with O
the O
NFL B-ORG
logo O
since O
Super B-MISC
Bowl I-MISC
XXXIX I-MISC
) O
, O
and O
the O
other O
officials O
wear O
black O
hats O
with O
white O
stripes O
. O

In O
a O
career O
of O
more O
than O
30 O
years O
, O
he O
had O
been O
a O
critic O
of O
the O
tensions O
embedded O
in O
his O
field O
of O
study O
, O
advocating O
Islamic B-MISC
modernism O
, O
secularism O
, O
and O
humanism O
. O

Joining O
him O
in O
the O
film O
were O
fellow O
action O
stars O
Jason B-PER
Statham I-PER
, O
Jet B-PER
Li I-PER
, O
and O
Dolph B-PER
Lundgren I-PER
, O
as O
well O
as O
Terry B-PER
Crews I-PER
, O
Mickey B-PER
Rourke I-PER
, O
Randy B-PER
Couture I-PER
, O
Eric B-PER
Roberts I-PER
, O
and O
Stone B-PER
Cold I-PER
Steve I-PER
Austin I-PER
, O
and O
cameos O
by O
fellow O
' O
80 O
s O
action O
icons O
Bruce B-PER
Willis I-PER
and O
Arnold B-PER
Schwarzenegger I-PER
. O

John B-PER
Locke I-PER
is O
sometimes O
considered O
the O
founder O
of O
this O
form O
. O

He O
also O
fulfilled O
his O
childhood O
dreams O
of O
being O
a O
sports O
announcer O
by O
performing O
the O
play-by-play O
commentary O
in O
the O
video O
game O
" O
NBA B-MISC
Ballers I-MISC
: I-MISC
Chosen I-MISC
One I-MISC
" O
on O
Xbox B-MISC
360 I-MISC
and O
PlayStation B-MISC
3 I-MISC
. O

Kris B-PER
Kristofferson I-PER
, O
who O
was O
working O
as O
a O
janitor O
in O
the O
studio O
at O
the O
time O
, O
was O
enlisted O
to O
hold O
the O
bongos O
in O
one O
hand O
and O
the O
cowbell O
in O
the O
other O
. O

Several O
national O
sporting O
bodies O
( O
e.g. O
the O
Spanish I-MISC
" O
Consejo B-ORG
Superior I-ORG
de I-ORG
Deportes I-ORG
" O
) O
also O
recognize O
chess O
as O
a O
sport O
. O

A O
live O
version O
of O
the O
song O
is O
available O
on O
the O
DVD O
" O
Live B-MISC
at I-MISC
Wembley I-MISC
July I-MISC
16 I-MISC
, I-MISC
1988 I-MISC
" O
. O

While O
living O
near O
his O
friends O
, O
Barrett B-PER
decided O
to O
write O
more O
songs O
( O
" O
Bike B-MISC
" O
was O
written O
around O
this O
time O
) O
. O

Irene B-PER
Cara I-PER
appeared O
during O
the O
first O
season O
( O
1971 O
– O
1972 O
) O
and O
would O
go O
on O
to O
become O
a O
pop-music O
star O
. O

The O
film O
was O
based O
on O
the O
Broadway B-MISC
play O
of O
the O
same O
name O
. O

The O
religious O
architecture O
of O
Angkor B-LOC
has O
characteristic O
structures O
, O
elements O
, O
and O
motifs O
, O
which O
are O
identified O
in O
the O
glossary O
below O
. O

The O
first O
known O
mention O
of O
the O
term O
' O
panspermia O
' O
was O
in O
the O
writings O
of O
the O
5th O
century O
BC O
Greek B-MISC
philosopher O
Anaxagoras B-PER
. O

Ancient O
Aram B-LOC
, O
bordering O
northern O
Israel B-LOC
and O
what O
is O
now O
called O
Syria B-LOC
, O
is O
considered O
the O
linguistic O
center O
of O
Aramaic B-MISC
, O
the O
language O
of O
the O
Arameans B-MISC
who O
settled O
the O
area O
during O
the O
Bronze B-MISC
Age I-MISC
circa O
3500 O
BC O
. O

He O
collaborated O
with O
fellow O
rap O
artist O
Tupac B-PER
Shakur I-PER
on O
the O
1996 O
single O
" O
2 B-MISC
of I-MISC
Amerikaz I-MISC
Most I-MISC
Wanted I-MISC
" O
. O

Nevertheless O
, O
maras O
have O
been O
greatly O
affected O
by O
hunting O
and O
habitat O
alteration O
and O
have O
been O
extirpated O
in O
some O
areas O
, O
including O
Buenos B-LOC
Aires I-LOC
Province I-LOC
. O

She O
was O
the O
co-founder O
and O
a O
leading O
member O
of O
the O
Turkish B-ORG
Historical I-ORG
Society I-ORG
. O

Finishing O
her O
work O
on O
that O
screenplay O
, O
she O
was O
hired O
by O
producer O
Hal B-PER
B. I-PER
Wallis I-PER
as O
a O
screenwriter O
and O
script-doctor O
. O

On O
January O
29 O
, O
2011 O
, O
professional O
boxer O
Timothy B-PER
Bradley I-PER
defended O
his O
WBO B-ORG
light O
welterweight O
title O
in O
a O
unification O
fight O
against O
WBC B-ORG
champion O
Devon B-PER
Alexander I-PER
. O

Stems O
carry O
leaves O
or O
the O
stems O
may O
be O
leafless O
( O
in O
" O
Caulanthus B-MISC
" O
) O
, O
and O
some O
species O
lack O
stems O
altogether O
. O

Traditionally O
, O
kouign-amann O
is O
baked O
as O
a O
large O
cake O
and O
served O
in O
slices O
, O
although O
recently O
, O
especially O
in O
North B-LOC
America I-LOC
, O
individual O
cupcake-sized O
pastries O
( O
kouignettes O
) O
have O
become O
more O
popular O
. O

It O
is O
one O
of O
the O
shortest O
books O
in O
the O
Bible B-MISC
: O
only O
1 O
chapter O
of O
25 O
verses O
long O
. O

Timișoara B-LOC
became O
highly O
industrialised O
both O
through O
new O
investments O
and O
by O
increasing O
the O
capacities O
of O
the O
old O
enterprises O
in O
various O
industries O
: O
machine O
building O
, O
textile O
and O
footwear O
, O
electrical O
, O
food O
, O
plastics O
, O
optical O
, O
building O
materials O
, O
furniture O
. O

After O
mid-January O
he O
lost O
his O
place O
in O
the O
starting O
eleven O
to O
fellow O
countryman O
Marek B-PER
Saganowski I-PER
, O
but O
finished O
the O
season O
as O
the O
club O
's O
top O
goalscorer O
with O
21 O
goals O
. O

The O
name O
in O
the O
Hindu B-MISC
zodiac O
is O
likewise O
" O
kumbha O
" O
" O
water-pitcher O
" O
. O

The O
emblem O
now O
appears O
on O
official O
stationery O
, O
publications O
and O
papers O
, O
and O
is O
stamped O
on O
various O
items O
in O
use O
in O
the O
Palace B-LOC
of I-LOC
Westminster I-LOC
, O
such O
as O
cutlery O
, O
silverware O
and O
china O
. O

The O
engines O
had O
two O
extra O
cylinders O
for O
forced O
induction O
, O
so O
they O
appeared O
like O
V6 B-MISC
engines O
but O
without O
spark O
plugs O
on O
the O
front O
cylinder O
pair O
. O

This O
genus O
has O
recently O
been O
eliminated O
by O
many O
authorities O
and O
is O
now O
occasionally O
also O
included O
in O
" O
Aquila B-PER
" O
, O
although O
not O
all O
ornithological O
unions O
have O
followed O
this O
suit O
in O
this O
re-classification O
. O

Evolutionary O
psychology O
has O
its O
historical O
roots O
in O
Charles B-PER
Darwin I-PER
's O
theory O
of O
natural O
selection O
. O

Hans B-PER
Jonas I-PER
described O
her O
as O
having O
a O
" O
genius O
for O
friendship O
" O
, O
and O
, O
in O
her O
own O
words O
, O
" O
" O
( O
love O
of O
friendship O
) O
. O

The O
species O
of O
this O
genus O
are O
found O
in O
the O
Holarctic B-LOC
ecozone O
. O

Australia B-LOC
accounts O
for O
more O
than O
half O
of O
the O
world O
's O
certified O
organic O
hectares O
. O

The O
geology O
of O
Bolivia B-LOC
comprises O
a O
variety O
of O
different O
lithologies O
as O
well O
as O
tectonic O
and O
sedimentary O
environments O
. O

Cranmer B-PER
was O
punished O
for O
his O
work O
in O
the O
English B-MISC
Reformation I-MISC
by O
being O
burned O
at O
the O
stake O
on O
21 O
March O
1556 O
. O

The O
critic O
Michael B-PER
Sragow I-PER
was O
full O
of O
praise O
for O
her O
work O
, O
writing O
that O
her O
performance O
was O
" O
the O
critical O
element O
that O
makes O
[ O
the O
film O
] O
necessary O
viewing O
" O
. O

In O
this O
view O
, O
Jews B-MISC
are O
charged O
with O
living O
a O
holy O
life O
as O
God B-PER
's O
priest-people O
. O

He O
developed O
concepts O
of O
plant O
morphology O
and O
classification O
, O
which O
did O
not O
withstand O
the O
scientific O
scrutiny O
of O
the O
Renaissance B-MISC
. O

This O
was O
not O
the O
only O
depiction O
of O
Little B-MISC
Red I-MISC
Riding I-MISC
Hood I-MISC
in O
an O
animated O
short O
. O

The O
relative O
concentrations O
of O
, O
and O
the O
deprotonated O
forms O
( O
bicarbonate O
) O
and O
( O
carbonate O
) O
depend O
on O
the O
pH. O
As O
shown O
in O
a O
Bjerrum B-PER
plot O
, O
in O
neutral O
or O
slightly O
alkaline O
water O
( O
pH O
> O
6.5 O
) O
, O
the O
bicarbonate O
form O
predominates O
( O
> O
50 O
% O
) O
becoming O
the O
most O
prevalent O
( O
> O
95 O
% O
) O
at O
the O
pH O
of O
seawater O
. O

The O
most O
common O
aboriginal O
language O
is O
Cree B-MISC
17,215 O
( O
0.53 O
% O
) O
. O

They O
were O
less O
successful O
than O
their O
English B-MISC
cousins O
due O
to O
rather O
different O
operating O
conditions O
and O
all O
were O
scrapped O
before O
the O
start O
of O
the O
preservation O
era O
. O

The O
French B-ORG
Army I-ORG
was O
of O
mixed O
quality O
. O

Another O
significant O
figure O
in O
the O
film O
who O
is O
directly O
named O
in O
the O
Gospels B-MISC
is O
Pontius B-PER
Pilate I-PER
, O
who O
is O
humorously O
given O
rhotacism O
. O

Her O
mother O
is O
of O
Polish B-MISC
descent O
, O
and O
her O
father O
has O
German B-MISC
, O
Scottish B-MISC
and O
Irish B-MISC
ancestry O
. O

He O
finished O
the O
game O
with O
34 O
points O
, O
including O
23 O
points O
in O
the O
4th O
quarter O
, O
just O
one O
point O
shy O
of O
Michael B-PER
Jordan I-PER
's O
franchise O
playoff O
record O
. O

On O
operating O
system O
Turkish-Qs B-MISC
, O
when O
using O
Turkish-F B-MISC
or O
keyboard O
layout O
[ O
[ O
keyboard O
layout O
] O
] O
s O
, O
it O
can O
be O
typed O
with O
the O
combination O
. O

Casemiro B-PER
gives O
a O
lot O
of O
balance O
, O
but O
not O
only O
that O
. O

In O
1709 O
he O
became O
professor O
of O
botany O
and O
medicine O
, O
and O
in O
that O
capacity O
he O
did O
good O
service O
, O
not O
only O
to O
his O
own O
university O
, O
but O
also O
to O
botanical O
science O
, O
by O
his O
improvements O
and O
additions O
to O
the O
botanic O
garden O
of O
Leiden B-LOC
, O
and O
by O
the O
publication O
of O
numerous O
works O
descriptive O
of O
new O
species O
of O
plants O
. O

In O
August O
2020 O
scientists O
reported O
that O
bacteria O
that O
feed O
on O
air O
discovered O
2017 O
in O
Antarctica B-LOC
are O
likely O
not O
limited O
to O
Antarctica B-LOC
after O
discovering O
the O
two O
genes O
previously O
linked O
to O
their O
" O
atmospheric O
chemosynthesis O
" O
in O
soil O
of O
two O
other O
similar O
cold O
desert O
sites O
, O
which O
provides O
further O
information O
on O
this O
carbon O
sink O
and O
further O
strengthens O
the O
extremophile O
evidence O
that O
supports O
the O
potential O
existence O
of O
microbial O
life O
on O
alien O
planets O
. O

The O
event O
was O
organized O
by O
Amos B-PER
Alonzo I-PER
Stagg I-PER
and O
sent O
invitations O
to O
state O
champion O
teams O
. O

Members O
of O
this O
genus O
share O
many O
characteristics O
and O
uses O
with O
members O
of O
the O
closely O
related O
genus O
" O
Celosia B-LOC
" O
. O

With O
two O
red O
cards O
throughout O
his O
international O
career O
, O
he O
is O
Italy B-LOC
's O
most O
red O
carded O
player O
ever O
, O
alongside O
Giancarlo B-PER
Antognoni I-PER
and O
Daniele B-PER
De I-PER
Rossi I-PER
. O

Calreticulin O
binds O
to O
antibodies O
in O
certain O
area O
of O
systemic O
lupus O
and O
Sjögren B-LOC
patients O
that O
contain O
anti-Ro O
/ O
SSA O
antibodies O
. O

" O
" O
Perfect O
10 O
" O
" O
is O
a O
song O
by O
The B-ORG
Beautiful I-ORG
South I-ORG
, O
released O
in O
1998 O
as O
the O
first O
single O
from O
their O
sixth O
studio O
album O
, O
" O
Quench B-MISC
" O
. O

He O
grew O
up O
a O
mile O
from O
West B-LOC
Ham I-LOC
Station I-LOC
. O

The O
total O
energy O
of O
a O
system O
is O
sometimes O
called O
the O
Hamiltonian O
, O
after O
William B-PER
Rowan I-PER
Hamilton I-PER
. O

Different O
Rodnover B-MISC
groups O
often O
have O
a O
preference O
for O
a O
particular O
deity O
over O
others O
. O

Lake B-LOC
Chad I-LOC
, O
after O
which O
the O
country O
is O
named O
( O
and O
which O
in O
turn O
takes O
its O
name O
from O
the O
Kanuri B-MISC
word O
for O
" O
lake O
" O
) O
, O
is O
the O
remains O
of O
an O
immense O
lake O
that O
occupied O
of O
the O
Chad B-LOC
Basin I-LOC
7,000 O
years O
ago O
. O

This O
is O
Pearl B-ORG
Jam I-ORG
's O
first O
album O
to O
feature O
former O
Soundgarden B-ORG
drummer O
Matt B-PER
Cameron I-PER
, O
who O
joined O
during O
1998 O
's O
Yield B-MISC
Tour I-MISC
to O
replace O
Jack B-PER
Irons I-PER
. O

In O
some O
cases O
, O
adult O
coyotes O
have O
been O
preyed O
upon O
by O
both O
American B-MISC
black O
and O
grizzly O
bears O
, O
American I-MISC
alligators O
, O
large O
Canada B-LOC
lynx O
and O
golden O
eagles O
. O

Thomas B-PER
Addison I-PER
was O
first O
to O
describe O
Addison B-PER
's O
disease O
in O
1849 O
. O

He O
pitched O
15 O
innings O
for O
the O
Cleveland B-ORG
Indians I-ORG
in O
1939 O
but O
gave O
up O
15 O
earned O
runs O
and O
was O
sent O
back O
down O
to O
the O
minors O
. O

From O
1946 O
until O
his O
death O
, O
he O
owned O
a O
25 O
% O
share O
of O
the O
Pittsburgh B-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
. O

It O
was O
produced O
and O
directed O
by O
Ron B-PER
Clements I-PER
and O
John B-PER
Musker I-PER
, O
and O
is O
based O
on O
the O
Arabic B-MISC
folktale O
of O
the O
same O
name O
from O
the O
" O
One B-MISC
Thousand I-MISC
and I-MISC
One I-MISC
Nights I-MISC
" O
. O

The O
159 O
contested O
the O
Bathurst B-MISC
12 I-MISC
Hour I-MISC
race O
for O
production O
cars O
in O
2007 O
, O
2009 O
and O
2010 O
. O

It O
turns O
west O
again O
to O
meet O
Swansea B-LOC
Bay I-LOC
at O
Porthcawl B-LOC
. O

In O
many O
ways O
, O
Wilhelm B-PER
was O
a O
victim O
of O
his O
inheritance O
and O
of O
Otto B-PER
von I-PER
Bismarck I-PER
's O
machinations O
. O

In O
1830 O
, O
Brussels B-LOC
became O
the O
capital O
of O
newly O
founded O
Belgium B-LOC
. O

The O
expanding O
cultural O
performance O
of O
the O
city O
was O
underscored O
by O
the O
relocation O
of O
the O
Universal B-ORG
Music I-ORG
Group I-ORG
who O
decided O
to O
move O
their O
headquarters O
to O
the O
banks O
of O
the O
River B-LOC
Spree B-LOC
. O

The O
Holocene B-LOC
, O
the O
current O
geological O
epoch O
, O
begins O
about O
11,700 O
years O
ago O
when O
the O
Pleistocene B-LOC
ends O
. O

In O
1872 O
, O
he O
resigned O
from O
the O
firm O
due O
to O
illness O
, O
and O
set O
sail O
for O
Europe B-LOC
in O
search O
of O
a O
cure O
. O

He O
scored O
his O
first O
goal O
of O
the O
season O
against O
Juventus B-ORG
, O
which O
was O
the O
winner O
in O
a O
1 O
– O
0 O
victory O
on O
25 O
November O
2012 O
. O

Outgoing O
Democratic B-MISC
President O
James B-PER
Buchanan I-PER
and O
the O
incoming O
Republicans B-MISC
rejected O
secession O
as O
illegal O
. O

The O
following O
season O
also O
saw O
the O
departure O
of O
Walter B-PER
Samuel I-PER
for O
€ O
25 O
" O
million O
and O
Emerson B-PER
for O
€ O
28 O
" O
million O
, O
which O
decreased O
the O
strength O
of O
the O
squad O
. O

In O
102 O
games O
with O
Iowa B-ORG
in O
2011 O
, O
he O
hit O
. O

A O
number O
of O
manufacturers O
have O
introduced O
hybrid O
engines O
, O
mainly O
involving O
a O
small O
gasoline O
engine O
coupled O
with O
an O
electric O
motor O
and O
with O
a O
large O
battery O
bank O
, O
but O
these O
too O
have O
yet O
to O
make O
much O
of O
an O
inroad O
into O
the O
market O
shares O
of O
gasoline I-MISC
and O
Diesel B-ORG
engines O
. O

The O
creation O
of O
Malaysia B-LOC
was O
the O
amalgamation O
of O
the O
Federation B-LOC
of I-LOC
Malaya I-LOC
( O
now O
West B-LOC
Malaysia B-LOC
) O
, O
Singapore B-LOC
and O
the O
crown O
colony O
/ O
British B-MISC
protectorates O
of O
North B-LOC
Borneo B-LOC
and O
Sarawak B-LOC
( O
collectively O
known O
as O
British B-LOC
Borneo B-LOC
, O
now O
East B-LOC
Malaysia I-LOC
) O
in O
September O
1963 O
. O

was O
later O
released O
on O
Mark B-PER
Lanegan I-PER
’s O
album O
, O
" O
The B-MISC
Winding I-MISC
Sheet I-MISC
" O
, O
in O
1990 O
. O

In O
the O
case O
of O
the O
T4 B-MISC
phage O
, O
the O
construction O
of O
new O
virus O
particles O
involves O
the O
assistance O
of O
helper O
proteins O
. O

Increased O
levels O
of O
skin O
cancer O
have O
been O
associated O
with O
arsenic O
exposure O
in O
Wisconsin B-LOC
, O
even O
at O
levels O
below O
the O
10 O
part O
per O
billion O
drinking O
water O
standard O
. O

Modern O
Christmas B-MISC
trees O
have O
been O
related O
to O
the O
" O
tree O
of O
paradise O
" O
of O
medieval O
mystery O
plays O
that O
were O
given O
on O
24 O
December O
, O
the O
commemoration O
and O
name O
day O
of O
Adam B-PER
and I-PER
Eve I-PER
in O
various O
countries O
. O

Chess B-MISC
has O
an O
extensive O
literature O
. O

Under O
Ezana B-PER
( O
fl. O
320 O
– O
360 O
) O
, O
Aksum B-LOC
later O
adopted O
Christianity B-MISC
. O

This O
view O
is O
known O
as O
the O
Friedman B-PER
doctrine O
. O

120 O
– O
220 O
) O
who O
defended O
their O
beliefs O
against O
critics O
and O
recommended O
their O
faith O
to O
outsiders O
were O
called O
Christian B-MISC
apologists O
. O

On O
November O
10 O
, O
2014 O
, O
Vicky B-PER
Morales I-PER
was O
hired O
an O
anchor O
. O

This O
tunic O
was O
pinned O
at O
the O
shoulders O
by O
brooches O
and O
had O
slit O
skirts O
which O
bared O
the O
thighs O
and O
permitted O
more O
freedom O
of O
movement O
than O
the O
voluminous O
Ionian B-MISC
chiton O
( O
costume O
) O
. O

Of O
the O
16 O
genes O
identified O
in O
these O
pathways O
, O
three O
were O
found O
to O
be O
dysregulated O
in O
the O
dorsolateral O
prefrontal O
cortex O
portion O
of O
the O
brain O
in O
post-mortem O
studies O
: O
" O
CACNA1C B-MISC
" O
, O
" O
GNG2 O
" O
, O
and O
" O
ITPR2 O
" O
. O

He O
accepted O
a O
position O
to O
once O
again O
manage O
the O
high O
level O
Class O
A O
Wilmington B-ORG
Blue I-ORG
Rocks I-ORG
minor O
league O
team O
for O
the O
2007 O
season O
. O

This O
name O
is O
formed O
by O
replacing O
the O
termination O
" O
- O
aceae O
" O
in O
the O
name O
Liliaceae B-MISC
by O
the O
termination O
" O
- O
opsida O
" O
( O
Art O
16 O
of O
the O
ICBN B-MISC
) O
. O

Contemporary O
reports O
give O
conflicting O
causes O
, O
such O
as O
that O
he O
succumbed O
to O
a O
stroke O
( O
which O
he O
had O
a O
year O
earlier O
) O
or O
to O
malaria O
, O
which O
he O
had O
contracted O
during O
a O
trip O
to O
the O
Southern B-LOC
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
. O

) O
can O
carry O
a O
number O
of O
pathogens O
, O
of O
which O
bubonic O
plague O
( O
via O
the O
Oriental B-MISC
rat O
flea O
) O
, O
typhus O
, O
Weil B-PER
's O
disease O
, O
toxoplasmosis O
and O
trichinosis O
are O
the O
best O
known O
. O

Antidepressant O
medications O
can O
reduce O
anxiety O
, O
and O
several O
selective O
serotonin O
reuptake O
inhibitors O
have O
been O
USFDA B-ORG
approved O
to O
treat O
various O
anxiety O
disorders O
. O

At O
the O
twin O
battles O
of O
Jena B-LOC
and O
Auerstedt B-LOC
, O
fought O
on O
14 O
October O
, O
the O
French B-MISC
convincingly O
defeated O
the O
Prussians B-MISC
and O
inflicted O
heavy O
casualties O
. O

A O
large O
pack O
of O
dholes O
descends O
on O
the O
jungle O
, O
destroying O
everything O
in O
its O
path. O
Mowgli B-PER
, O
however O
, O
decides O
that O
he O
and O
Akela B-PER
should O
prepare O
the O
wolf O
pack O
to O
battle O
the O
dhole O
tribes O
, O
with O
Baloo B-PER
concurring O
with O
Akela B-PER
's O
orders O
. O

Against O
these O
600 O
sorties O
the O
" O
Luftwaffe B-ORG
" O
on O
average O
flew O
1,500 O
sorties O
a O
day O
. O

One O
example O
is O
the O
Shakespeare-aficionado O
Chang B-PER
in O
" O
Star B-MISC
Trek I-MISC
VI I-MISC
: I-MISC
The I-MISC
Undiscovered I-MISC
Country I-MISC
" O
( O
1991 O
) O
, O
a O
Klingon B-MISC
, O
who O
quotes O
Shylock B-MISC
. O

Juggling O
and O
ball O
games O
were O
popular O
with O
children O
, O
and O
wrestling O
is O
also O
documented O
in O
a O
tomb O
at O
Beni B-LOC
Hasan I-LOC
. O

Since O
December O
1944 O
( O
Battle B-MISC
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
Bulge I-MISC
) O
, O
proximity O
fuzed O
artillery O
shells O
have O
been O
available O
that O
take O
the O
guesswork O
out O
of O
this O
process O
. O

It O
is O
one O
of O
eight O
genera O
in O
the O
tribe O
Poranthereae B-MISC
. O

Amillennialism O
, O
in O
Christian B-MISC
eschatology B-MISC
, O
involves O
the O
rejection O
of O
the O
belief O
that O
Jesus B-PER
will O
have O
a O
literal O
, O
thousand-year-long O
, O
physical O
reign O
on O
the O
earth O
. O

However O
, O
he O
rejected O
his O
old O
club O
's O
offer O
, O
and O
decided O
to O
stay O
at O
Arsenal B-MISC
in O
the O
expectation O
he O
would O
remain O
part O
of O
their O
side O
. O

Leicester B-LOC
's O
garment O
district O
is O
home O
to O
more O
than O
1,000 O
factories O
employing O
as O
many O
as O
10,000 O
workers O
. O

The O
original O
choice O
for O
the O
lead O
female O
role O
was O
Trisha B-PER
, O
who O
was O
replaced O
by O
Vedhika B-PER
. O

Kathryn B-PER
Bigelow I-PER
is O
attached O
to O
the O
project O
to O
produce O
and O
helm O
. O

He O
played O
12 O
times O
for O
Spain B-LOC
, O
scoring O
17 O
goals O
. O

In O
2006 O
, O
the O
BBC B-ORG
reconvened O
the O
original O
cast O
for O
a O
special O
one-off O
80-minute O
special O
, O
looking O
at O
what O
had O
happened O
to O
the O
lead O
characters O
in O
the O
intervening O
ten O
years O
. O

Graham B-PER
Linehan I-PER
and O
Stephen B-PER
Merchant I-PER
appear O
twice O
as O
the O
hospital O
porter O
and O
chef O
respectively O
. O

In O
May O
2010 O
, O
a O
new O
species O
, O
" O
Homo O
gautengensis O
" O
, O
was O
discovered O
in O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
. O

This O
category O
contains O
articles O
about O
sports O
venues O
in O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
. O

He O
was O
named O
in O
the O
team O
of O
the O
tournament O
by O
UEFA B-ORG
. O

- O
was O
exceeded O
only O
by O
Richard B-PER
Nixon I-PER
in O
his O
1972 O
victory O
over O
George B-PER
McGovern I-PER
. O

The O
VNQDĐ B-ORG
had O
previously O
attempted O
to O
engage O
in O
clandestine O
activities O
to O
undermine O
French B-MISC
rule O
, O
but O
increasing O
French B-MISC
scrutiny O
of O
their O
activities O
led O
to O
their O
leadership O
group O
taking O
the O
risk O
of O
staging O
a O
large O
scale O
military O
attack O
in O
the O
Red B-LOC
River I-LOC
Delta I-LOC
in O
northern O
Vietnam B-LOC
. O

They O
were O
revived O
shortly O
after O
Boris B-PER
Johnson I-PER
's O
re-election O
as O
Mayor O
in O
May O
2012 O
, O
but O
six O
months O
later O
they O
were O
cancelled O
again O
. O

During O
his O
time O
with O
Integrál-DAC B-ORG
he O
finished O
with O
11 O
goals O
as O
the O
club O
's O
top O
goal O
scorer O
. O

The O
band O
subsequently O
released O
" O
No B-MISC
Code I-MISC
" O
in O
1996 O
and O
" O
Yield B-MISC
" O
in O
1998 O
. O

At O
that O
time O
, O
Alabama B-LOC
and O
many O
other O
states O
had O
to O
change O
their O
legislative O
districting O
, O
as O
many O
across O
the O
country O
had O
systems O
that O
underrepresented O
urban O
areas O
and O
districts O
. O

There O
is O
a O
population O
in O
Scandinavia B-LOC
that O
includes O
bears O
of O
the O
western O
and O
eastern O
lineages O
. O

In O
a O
notable O
appearance O
July O
30 O
against O
the O
Boston B-ORG
Red I-ORG
Sox I-ORG
he O
recorded O
the O
final O
seven O
outs O
on O
fifty O
pitches O
to O
complete O
a O
5 O
– O
2 O
win O
. O

Modern O
players O
such O
as O
Ryan B-PER
Martinie I-PER
of O
heavy O
metal O
band O
Mudvayne B-ORG
have O
used O
similar O
techniques O
. O

The O
Corinthian B-LOC
order O
was O
raised O
to O
rank O
by O
the O
writings O
of O
Vitruvius B-PER
in O
the O
1st O
century O
BC O
. O

Having O
made O
the O
proper O
preparations O
, O
in O
April O
716 O
, O
he O
fell O
upon O
the O
triumphant O
army O
near O
Malmedy B-LOC
as O
it O
was O
returning O
to O
its O
own O
province O
. O

After O
the O
Arizona B-ORG
game O
, O
they O
would O
then O
win O
eight O
straight O
home O
games O
against O
unranked O
opponents O
. O

At O
Quebec B-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
it O
is O
. O

He O
was O
signed O
by O
Reading B-ORG
three O
years O
later O
at O
age O
18 O
, O
where O
he O
played O
in O
the O
reserves O
. O

Due O
to O
the O
simplicity O
of O
the O
design O
( O
two O
intersecting O
lines O
) O
, O
cross-shaped O
incisions O
make O
their O
appearance O
from O
deep O
prehistory O
; O
as O
cults O
in O
European B-LOC
Upper I-LOC
Paleolithic I-LOC
caves O
, O
dating O
back O
to O
the O
beginning O
of O
the O
Iron B-LOC
Age I-LOC
, O
and O
throughout O
prehistory O
to O
the O
crux O
gammata O
. O

To O
the O
east O
and O
southeast O
is O
the O
Baltic B-LOC
Sea I-LOC
. O

Its O
members O
were O
elected O
at O
local O
and O
regional O
levels O
, O
although O
part O
of O
them O
were O
assigned O
by O
Gaddafi B-PER
personally O
. O

He O
is O
the O
father O
of O
Gabriele B-PER
, O
who O
was O
also O
a O
professional O
footballer O
. O

The O
first O
job O
in O
operating O
Colossus B-MISC
for O
a O
new O
message O
was O
to O
prepare O
the O
paper O
tape O
loop O
. O

Renault B-ORG
was O
innovative O
during O
this O
period O
producing O
non-standard O
designs O
such O
as O
the O
111 O
° O
10-cylinder O
engine O
for O
the O
2003 O
RS23 O
which O
was O
designed O
to O
effectively O
lower O
the O
center O
of O
gravity O
of O
the O
engine O
and O
thus O
improve O
the O
car O
's O
handling O
. O

She O
has O
sat O
on O
the O
board O
of O
directors O
of O
the O
United B-ORG
Nations I-ORG
Research I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
for I-ORG
Social I-ORG
Development I-ORG
. O

He O
was O
also O
loaned O
to O
Wycombe B-ORG
Wanderers I-ORG
earlier O
in O
the O
season O
. O

Two O
large O
gyres O
, O
one O
in O
the O
northern O
hemisphere O
flowing O
clockwise O
and O
one O
south O
of O
the O
equator O
moving O
anticlockwise O
( O
including O
the O
Agulhas B-LOC
Current I-LOC
and O
Agulhas B-LOC
Return I-LOC
Current I-LOC
) O
, O
constitute O
the O
dominant O
flow O
pattern O
. O

In O
2007 O
, O
it O
was O
named O
the O
second-most O
visually O
influential O
film O
of O
all O
time O
by O
the O
Visual B-ORG
Effects I-ORG
Society I-ORG
. O

At O
the O
Academy B-ORG
of I-ORG
Country I-ORG
Music I-ORG
, O
she O
has O
won O
seven O
awards O
and O
39 O
nominations O
. O

Following O
the O
end O
of O
the O
Peloponnesian B-MISC
War I-MISC
, O
404 O
" O
BC O
, O
it O
was O
replaced O
by O
the O
land O
tortoise O
. O

The O
team O
went O
into O
the O
penultimate O
match O
of O
the O
season O
needing O
to O
beat O
promotion O
rivals O
Sunderland B-ORG
to O
have O
a O
chance O
of O
going O
up O
. O

He O
attended O
the O
Stamp B-MISC
Act I-MISC
Congress I-MISC
in O
1765 O
and O
served O
on O
the O
committee O
that O
drafted O
an O
address O
to O
the O
King O
arguing O
the O
right O
of O
the O
colonies O
to O
decide O
tax O
policies O
for O
themselves O
. O

KEMI B-ORG
's O
proposal O
was O
ultimately O
declined O
. O

He O
emigrated O
from O
the O
USSR B-LOC
in O
1975 O
. O

In O
Keynesian B-PER
theory O
, O
increased O
employment O
results O
in O
increased O
aggregate O
demand O
( O
AD O
) O
, O
which O
leads O
to O
further O
hiring O
by O
firms O
to O
increase O
output O
. O

The O
duo O
released O
their O
second O
album O
" O
Ice B-MISC
on I-MISC
the I-MISC
Dune I-MISC
" O
on O
17 O
June O
2013 O
. O

, O
which O
is O
also O
promoted O
by O
Procter B-ORG
& I-ORG
Gamble I-ORG
. O

On O
September O
29 O
, O
2010 O
, O
" O
Entertainment B-MISC
Weekly I-MISC
" O
writer O
Michael B-PER
Ausiello I-PER
reported O
that O
a O
movie O
would O
not O
happen O
. O

but O
characterises O
Hegelian B-PER
self-development O
as O
unduly O
" O
spiritual O
" O
and O
abstract O
. O

The O
river O
turns O
to O
the O
west O
near O
Arezzo B-LOC
passing O
through O
Florence B-LOC
, O
Empoli B-LOC
and O
Pisa B-LOC
, O
flowing O
into O
the O
Tyrrhenian B-LOC
Sea I-LOC
at O
Marina B-LOC
di I-LOC
Pisa I-LOC
. O

According O
to O
the O
book O
, O
the O
Americas B-LOC
are O
portrayed O
as O
a O
" O
land O
of O
promise O
" O
, O
the O
world O
's O
most O
exceptional O
land O
of O
the O
time O
. O

For O
example O
, O
in O
the O
Elkhorn B-LOC
Slough I-LOC
at O
Monterey B-LOC
Bay I-LOC
, O
cancrid O
crabs O
and O
innkeeper O
worms O
are O
mostly O
eaten O
in O
winter O
and O
spring O
, O
fish O
eggs O
from O
winter O
to O
early O
summer O
, O
bony O
fish O
in O
summer O
, O
and O
grapsid O
crabs O
and O
clams O
in O
fall O
. O

It O
is O
the O
only O
district O
in O
Ohio B-LOC
under O
direct O
control O
of O
the O
mayor O
, O
who O
appoints O
a O
school O
board O
. O

For O
further O
particulars O
see O
Publicani B-PER
. O

The O
national O
team O
plays O
its O
home O
games O
at O
the O
Ghazi B-LOC
Stadium I-LOC
in O
Kabul B-LOC
, O
while O
football O
in O
Afghanistan B-LOC
is O
governed O
by O
the O
Afghanistan B-ORG
Football I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
. O

The O
Siphnian B-LOC
Treasury I-LOC
was O
dedicated O
by O
the O
city O
of O
Siphnos B-LOC
whose O
citizens O
gave O
a O
tithe O
of O
the O
yield O
from O
their O
silver O
mines O
until O
the O
mines O
came O
to O
an O
abrupt O
end O
when O
the O
sea O
flooded O
the O
workings O
. O

He O
returned O
to O
Everton B-ORG
in O
August O
1982 O
for O
£ O
100,000 O
. O

It O
also O
does O
not O
appear O
to O
have O
been O
negatively O
impacted O
by O
fishing O
off O
southern O
Australia B-LOC
. O

Some O
non-native O
mustards O
, O
such O
as O
garlic O
mustard O
, O
" O
Alliaria O
petiolata O
" O
, O
an O
extremely O
invasive O
species O
in O
the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
, O
can O
be O
toxic O
to O
their O
larvae O
. O

It O
was O
alleged O
that O
he O
had O
thrown O
a O
punch O
at O
Frank B-PER
Lampard I-PER
. O

The O
railcars O
reduced O
the O
journey O
time O
between O
Auckland B-LOC
and O
Whangarei B-LOC
to O
4 O
hours O
and O
10 O
minutes O
, O
but O
mechanical O
faults O
with O
the O
railcars O
and O
the O
1959 O
opening O
of O
the O
Auckland B-LOC
Harbour I-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
meant O
that O
the O
railcars O
did O
not O
have O
a O
long O
future O
. O

Conspiracy O
theories O
are O
widely O
present O
on O
the O
Web B-MISC
in O
the O
form O
of O
blogs O
and O
YouTube I-MISC
videos O
, O
as O
well O
as O
on O
social O
media O
. O

Nine O
of O
52 O
matches O
were O
played O
in O
Edmonton B-LOC
, O
including O
a O
quarterfinal O
and O
a O
semifinal O
, O
and O
two O
of O
Canada B-LOC
. O

Drummer O
Ronnie B-PER
Vannucci I-PER
Jr. I-PER
is O
credited O
with O
creating O
the O
fast-paced O
drum O
beat O
in O
the O
first O
twenty-two O
seconds O
. O

The O
most O
abundant O
thorium O
minerals O
are O
thorianite O
( O
ThO O
) O
, O
thorite O
( O
ThSiO O
) O
and O
monazite O
, O
( O
( O
Th O
, O
Ca O
, O
Ce O
) O
PO B-LOC
) O
. O

However O
it O
was O
in O
private O
ownership O
, O
as O
was O
the O
harbour O
at O
Portreath B-LOC
, O
and O
was O
not O
made O
available O
to O
the O
proprietors O
of O
competing O
mines O
. O

She O
was O
appointed O
to O
Neil B-PER
Kinnock I-PER
's O
Shadow B-ORG
Cabinet I-ORG
shortly O
afterwards O
; O
she O
was O
elected O
Deputy O
Leader O
of O
the O
Labour B-ORG
Party I-ORG
in O
1992 O
, O
becoming O
the O
first O
woman O
to O
hold O
that O
role O
. O

In O
Darwin B-PER
's O
second O
year O
at O
the O
university O
he O
joined O
the O
Plinian B-ORG
Society I-ORG
, O
a O
student O
natural-history O
group O
featuring O
lively O
debates O
in O
which O
radical O
democratic O
students O
with O
materialistic O
views O
challenged O
orthodox O
religious O
concepts O
of O
science O
. O

The O
classical O
Zodiac O
is O
a O
revision O
of O
Neo-Babylonian B-MISC
constellations O
from O
the O
6th O
century O
BC O
. O

Their O
first O
two O
children O
were O
born O
before O
Elizabeth B-PER
succeeded O
her O
father O
as O
monarch O
in O
1952 O
: O
Prince O
Charles B-PER
in O
1948 O
and O
Princess O
Anne B-PER
in O
1950 O
. O

The O
Sanjoaninas I-MISC
Festivities I-MISC
in O
Angra B-LOC
do I-LOC
Heroísmo I-LOC
on O
Terceira B-LOC
are O
held O
in O
June O
honoring O
Saint B-PER
Anthony I-PER
, O
Saint B-PER
Peter I-PER
and O
Saint B-PER
John I-PER
the I-PER
Baptist I-PER
, O
in O
a O
large O
religious O
celebration O
. O

In O
Cuba B-LOC
, O
if O
a O
computer O
user O
at O
a O
government-controlled O
Internet B-MISC
cafe O
types O
certain O
words O
, O
the O
word O
processor O
or O
web O
browser O
is O
automatically O
closed O
, O
and O
a O
" O
state O
security O
" O
warning O
is O
given O
. O

Plans O
for O
the O
service O
to O
Frankfurt B-LOC
seem O
to O
have O
been O
shelved O
in O
2018 O
. O

He O
was O
elected O
as O
a O
Mississippi B-LOC
representative O
and O
senator O
, O
was O
a O
fixture O
of O
Mississippi B-LOC
high O
society O
, O
and O
a O
personal O
friend O
of O
Jefferson B-PER
Davis I-PER
. O

The O
Providence B-ORG
Journal I-ORG
Company I-ORG
bought O
channel O
17 O
in O
1979 O
. O

Croquet O
became O
highly O
popular O
as O
a O
social O
pastime O
in O
England B-LOC
during O
the O
1860 O
s O
. O

His O
unequal O
fight O
against O
them O
won O
the O
esteem O
of O
Europe B-LOC
also O
among O
others O
financial O
and O
military O
aid O
from O
the O
Papacy B-LOC
and O
Naples B-LOC
, O
Venice B-LOC
and O
Ragusa B-LOC
. O

Banda B-LOC
Aceh I-LOC
, O
the O
closest O
major O
city O
was O
particularly O
affected O
, O
suffering O
severe O
casualties O
. O

As O
at O
2018 O
Chad B-LOC
had O
a O
total O
of O
44,000 O
" O
km O
of O
roads O
of O
which O
approximately O
260 O
" O
km O
are O
paved O
. O

The O
instruments O
on O
Apollo B-MISC
11 I-MISC
were O
not O
as O
extensive O
or O
designed O
to O
operate O
long O
term O
. O

This O
policy O
proved O
deeply O
divisive O
as O
it O
forced O
Alberta B-LOC
to O
sell O
low-priced O
oil O
to O
eastern O
Canada B-LOC
. O

A O
study O
identified O
plague O
as O
a O
major O
cause O
of O
mortality O
in O
reintroduced O
populations O
in O
Colorado B-LOC
. O

For O
instance O
several O
excitatory O
ionotropic O
ligand-gated O
neurotransmitter O
receptors O
including O
glutamate O
receptors O
( O
AMPA O
, O
NMDA O
, O
and O
kainate O
) O
, O
nicotinic O
acetylcholine O
( O
nACh O
) O
, O
and O
serotonin O
( O
5-HT O
) O
receptors O
are O
nonselective O
cation O
channels O
that O
pass O
Na B-LOC
and O
K O
in O
nearly O
equal O
proportions O
, O
giving O
an O
equilibrium O
potential O
close O
to O
zero O
. O

Later O
though O
, O
they O
are O
depicted O
as O
being O
visible O
by O
regular O
people O
and O
as O
inspiring O
faith O
in O
the O
Buddha B-PER
. O

His O
hitting O
was O
one O
of O
the O
few O
bright O
spots O
for O
a O
Kansas B-ORG
City I-ORG
team O
that O
averaged O
94 O
defeats O
each O
season O
from O
1960 O
through O
1963 O
. O

" O
Buuz O
" O
are O
prepared O
in O
the O
weeks O
before O
and O
left O
outside O
to O
freeze O
; O
they O
are O
consumed O
with O
salads O
and O
fried O
bread O
, O
accompanied O
by O
" O
suutei O
tsai O
" O
( O
Mongolian B-MISC
tea O
) O
and O
vodka O
. O

In O
1876 O
, O
physicist O
John B-PER
Tyndall I-PER
also O
contributed O
to O
this O
field O
. O

Until O
the O
1980 O
s O
, O
Slovenia B-LOC
enjoyed O
relatively O
broad O
autonomy O
within O
the O
federation O
. O

While O
the O
family O
was O
nominally O
Orthodox B-MISC
, O
it O
had O
little O
religious O
fervor O
. O

He O
was O
the O
first O
Congressman O
to O
serve O
while O
having O
a O
father O
in O
the O
Senate B-ORG
. O

Some O
38 O
% O
of O
Ecuador B-LOC
's O
land O
is O
forested O
, O
and O
despite O
a O
1.5 O
% O
annual O
deforestation O
rate O
remains O
one O
of O
the O
most O
biodiverse O
locations O
on O
the O
planet O
. O

Subsequently O
, O
he O
became O
known O
as O
" O
Israel B-LOC
's O
founding O
father O
" O
. O

It O
is O
spoken O
as O
a O
second O
language O
by O
inhabitants O
of O
Zaragoza B-LOC
, O
Huesca B-LOC
, O
Ejea B-LOC
de I-LOC
los I-LOC
Caballeros I-LOC
, O
or O
Teruel B-LOC
. O

Historical O
facts O
about O
Tansen B-PER
are O
difficult O
to O
extract O
from O
the O
extensive O
and O
contradictory O
legends O
that O
surround O
him O
. O
